Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 12.11.07 15:57:22
OCR By XXX@HDChina! Sorry for a limited time.
(WHIMPERING)
(CHAINSAW REVVING)
(CHAINSAW BUZZING)abc(THUDDING)
故事结束时我未必活着。
OPHELIA: Just because I'm te II ing y o u this st o ry
d o esn't mean I'm a I ive at the end o f it.
记录海洋
This c o u I d a II be pre-rec o rded
and I c o u I d be ta I king t o y o u fr o m the b o tt o m o f the o cean.
一个故事
Yeah, it's that kind o f a st o ry.
事情失控。
Because things just g o t s o o ut o f c o ntr oI.
让我们返回abc一切开始。
But I et's g o back t o where it started.abcHere, in paradise.
在天上。
说神在第七日完蛋
Where they say
G o d parked Himse I f
o n the seventh day,
但可能第八天捏造了...
but they t o wed
Him o n the eighth.
野兽
避难奔abc春大海。
And this is Ben and Ch o n's
h oI e-in-the-wa II by the sea.
以现金购买。
Paid f o r in cash.
(WOMAN MOANING)
我不坏海逸年幼孩子。
N o t bad f o r tw o
y o ung Laguna dudes
肯定不会abc经纪人在华尔街上。
wh o are definite I y n o t
emp Io yab I e o n Wa II Street.
春杀手锏。
Ch o n is a ki II er.
2 RAID：伊拉克阿富汗。
Tw o t o urs. I raq, Afghanistan.
回来了很多钱。
And he came back with a Io t o f cash,
但没有...
but n o s o u I.
只是试图abc摆脱那些记忆。
He's a I ways trying t o fuck the war o ut o f himse I f.
我有一个高潮，
I have o rgasms.
他guerrasmo。
He has war-gasms.
所以，我尝试abc他已经失去了东西给他。
S o, I guess I try t o give him back
s o me o f the things that he's Io st.
春爱我生命。
Ch o n is the Io ve o f my I ife.
呼叫，我名字奥菲莉亚。
Ca II me O.abcI was named after O phe I ia,
一个远房亲戚，abc自杀身亡。
the bip oI ar basket-case in Hamlet, wh o c o mmitted suicide.
所以，我只是abc缩短至O。
S o I cut it d o wn t o just O.
草应该是坏，但...
D o pe's supp o sed t o be bad,
在这个世界上烂
but in a bad, bad w o r I d, it's g oo d.
是件好事。
Ch o n says drugs are a rati o na I resp o nse t o insanity.
春说，药是abc一个理性响应allinsanita。
Mmm.
(JAUNTY MUSIC PLAYING)
春你想一些吗？
Chon, you want some?
什么是打扰你这么多吗？
What is it about porn that you guys like so much?
是什么？
What is that?
- E在伊拉克？abc- 不..墨西哥。
Is that Iraq?
No. Mexico.
本？它不应该abc还维尔马吗？
Where's Ben?
Isn't he still in Burma?
不..
No. Africa, someplace.
在非洲某个地方abc保存...非洲人。
Saving Africans.
他说，他会abc回到3周。
He said he was
going to be gone
three weeks.
他改变了主意。
That's changing, O.
让我们去抽草。
Let's get some air.
来吧。
Come on.
我想，现在你abc思想，他们是如何生活在这个地方吗？
OPHELIA: I guess y o u've
figured o ut by n o w,
if pe o p I e are wi II ing t o g o
"Henry V III" o n this,
春Ben，培养abc在世界上最好草。
Ch o n and Ben gr o w
s o me o f the best
weed in the w o r I d.
(JAUNTY MUSIC PLAYING)
(HORN HONKS)
行李吗？abc谢谢
Bring the bags in. Thanks.
- 哦，你这个本abc- 本
OPHELIA: O h, yeah, this is Ben.
爱我生命。
Ben!
The o ther Io ve o f my I ife.
哦，我亲爱莲花
Oh, my sweet lotus.
我亲爱本
Oh, my sweet Ben.
非洲怎么样？
How was Africa?
你知道，我开始我维尔马abc坏了，我发现自己在刚果。
You know,
I started in Burma
and then I took a left and ended up in the Congo.
欢迎回本。 512室。 BelleabcVue Hotel酒店。 明天下午2
But if you're serious...
Good thing I'm tough.
- 春，我朋友abc- 很高兴见到你
Chon-boy.
Good to see you.
即使我
It's good to see you, man.
非常。
You all right?
Here, look.
- 你有没有开始做家庭吗？abc- 自制？当然，我打扫你房间。
You got any
of that Lomotil?
Lomotil? Yeah,
I put some in your room.
Suck on some
ice cubes, man.
- 你是狗屎。abc- 这是？
You look like shit.
Yeah?
Mmm-hmm.
这个地方是保持了良好增长。
Place looks good, though.abcThank you, O.
- 谢谢O。abc- 谢谢你。
Thank you.
什么也没有。
You're welcome.
你是个白痴。他什么也没做
Shut up. You're a jerk.
He didn't do anything.
我知道，我知道。你有没有abc我照顾我小？
I know, I know.
Here, you've been taking care of my babies?
Huh?
太忙了别东西，是吧？
Too busy making some of your own?
(SCOFFS)
听着，我会照顾他们。
Listen, I'm going to
go catch a long swim.
我们需要谈谈业务，好吗？
We'll talk
business later, okay?
Hey.
每一个成功公司abc一个伟大过去抛在脑后。
OPHELIA: Every successfu I business has an o rigin st o ry.
微软苹果abc出生于一个车库。
Micr o s o ft and App I e were b o rn in garages.
本春出生在沙滩上。
Ben and Ch o n's was b o rn o n the beach.
本了两个学位伯克利分校，abc在市场营销植物学。
Ben went t oabcBerke I ey and d o ub I e-maj o red in business and b o tany.
春还没有决定。
Ch o n was between dep Io yments.
高中朋友，
And they've been buddies since high sch ooI.
一天，他们坐在abc在这里，想过做什么
S o o ne day, they're sitting there
thinking ab o ut what they're g o ing t o d o, and Ben says...
- Ben说...abc- 你认为它得到了最好草
So where do you think the best cannabis in the world comes from?
- 世界？abc- 易...阿富汗。
Easy.
Afghanistan.
这是决定命运时刻。
Ding! That was the "f o under" m o ment.
更所以，春abc危险世界，
S o, Ch o n, fr o m the m o st danger o us gr o und in the w o r I d,
进行最好种子。
smugg I es back the finest seeds.
他们长大...在六年内开设了一对夫妇abc农作物客户一个很大很圆。
I t grew.
Within six years, they had a c o up I e o f farms
and a great cust o mer base.
Yo, try this.
成为一个城市传奇。
I t became urban I egend.
如果你问别人什么abc二十一世纪最佳贸易，
I f y o u ask any seri o us head
where the best d o pe in the w o r I d in the 21st century is,
不能泰国将牙买加abc肯定不是墨西哥...
it's n o t Thai I and, Jamaica, and certain I y n o t Mexic o.
CAC33％左右。
THC is testing 33%.
我们两倍左右，abc必须是错误
I ran it twice.
There's got to be
a glitch.
我认为我们只是发现了金矿。
I think we just struck gold.
在加州。
I t's right here in Ca I if o rnia, USA.
U.S.A.
本说，每abc植物需要爱。
Ben says every p I ant needs Io ve.
感觉就像策展人。
He sees himse I f as a hea I er.
当我开始abc帮助增长
Then when I started t o he I p o ut at the gr o w-o p,
他打电话给我，他莲花。
he ca II ed me his o wn Io tus in water.
我很喜欢。
I I ike that.
我们有很多客户abc从整个加州。
They partner in severa I dispensaries
and supp I y many o f the c I ubs in Ca I if o rnia.
不断增加...abc因为从我理解
And it's pr o gressive
because fr o m whatabcI've seen, at I east,
，有助于对抗疼痛。
it he I ps with the pain.
15万满意客户abc不可能是一个巧合。
Fifteen mi II i o n satisfied cust o mers can't a II be wr o ng.
但最大收获abc从装运到其他国家。
But the big m o ney c o mes fr o m shipping it o ut o f state.
我15。
That's the 50.
价格已经达到abc6000美元一磅。
At high prices, they get up t o $6,000 a p o und.
理念Benabc佛教做法。
Ben's guiding phi Io s o phy is basica II y Buddhist.
我不跟人开玩笑。
D o n't fuck with pe o p I e.
他天才是保持99％abc问题暴力业务。
His true genius is that he takes 99%
o f the paran o ia and vi oI ence o ut o f the business.
1％... 就在这里abc在春。
The o ther 1%?
That's where Ch o n c o mes in.
理念春是最糟糕。
Ch o n's phi Io s o phy is basica II y Baddhist.
您打破了，混蛋
WOMAN: Get off me, fucker!
我不开玩笑了本。
D o n't fuck with Ben.
What?
钱...弗雷德
The money, Brett.
我欠你他妈钱
I got your fucking money.
(GUN COCKING)
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
本草业绿色。
OPHELIA: F o r Ben, the d o pe business is green.
他基金会abc在非洲亚洲位置。
His f o undati o n has branches in Africa and Asia.
钱是不足够...他说。
"M o ney isn't en o ugh, " he says.
您，让您心。
"Y o u've g o t t o give y o ur heart."
OPHELIA: Hey, don't ever go away on me again.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
我认真地想念你。
I really missed you.
Ripetimelo。
Tell me that again.
我...
I
你真...
really
失败。
missed you.
知道您想法...婊子对吗？
OPHELIA: I kn o w what y o u're thinking.
"S I ut, " right?
也许错了，
And maybe it is wr o ng.
但事实我们爱你这么多。
But the truth is we a IIIo ve each o ther s o much.
我们相信，我们之间。
We trust each o ther, we take care o f each o ther.
我们照顾我们。
我...一起abc是一个完美男人。
And f o r me, t o gether they are o ne c o mp I ete man.
春冰冷金属，
Ch o n is c oI d meta I.
本温暖木地板。
Ben is warm w oo d.
本春扫帚，使爱。
Ch o n fucks
and Ben makes Io ve.
春地球。
Ch o n is earth
本精神。
and Ben, spirit.
有一个共同点...
And the o ne thing they have in c o mm o n
我。
is me.
我唯一爱他们生活。
I am the h o me that neither o f them ever had.
是我。
And they're mine.
我真很想念你在一起。
I really missed this
with you.
游泳吗？
Good swim?
太棒了。
Exhilarating.
没有鲨鱼？
No sharks?
不是在海洋中。
Not in the ocean.
他们知道你要来。
They knew
you were coming.
他们要满足...明天。
They want to meet.
Tomorrow.
我们做了一笔交易。
Let's make a deal.
大错。
Big mistake.
真相是，我们abc半个狗屁春。
Are we really
going to get caught up
in this shit, Chon?
我们希望得到循环吗？abc以任何方式，我们可以做到这一点。
We could get out of a business we want to get out of anyway.
如果不这样做，会发生什么事abc我已经准备好了？
What if I'm not
ready to walk away?
(SCOFFS)
- 所以你拉回来吗？abc- 不，我不知道。
Then you run it.
是，然后让我做abc我做最好。这样行吗？
That's not what I do.
Then let me do whatabcI do best, all right?
我们建立了这一切，我们。
We built this, it's ours.
因为你他妈想放弃一切吗？
Why the fuck do you
want to give it away?
- 你有没有看到视频吗？abc- 你，但我见过更糟。
You see that video?
I've seen worse
and I'd do worse to them.
好了：我不希望看到他们。
Yeah, and I wouldn't.
他们会认为我们怕他们。
They're going to think
we're afraid of them.
- 我怕他们。abc- 我不知道。
I am afraid of them.
我们是不是都像你这样春，我不想abc这个东西杀了人。
I'm not.
We're not all you, Chon.
I didn't get into this
thing to kill people.
你不明白吗？这就像在丛林中abc那么，当他们嗅到你恐惧
You don't get it, do you?
It's a jungle thing, Ben.
他喜欢攻击我们abc像一些野生他妈。
When they smell your fear, they like it.
They will attack us.
They're fucking savages.
收益率不为失败，春。
Surrender
is not defeat, Chon.
改变你头脑，保持安全。
You're resisting change.abcJust let it go.
停止争论。
Uh-oh. Testosterone.
关闭你腿，你看到一切。
Close your legs,
it's showing.
呃，对不起
Sorry.
覆盖从他自己
I was talking to him.
嘿，你们带给我abc在今晚一些不错地方？
Hey, can you boys take me out somewhere nice?
让我们去...我们可以喝abc一个小，放松
Come on.abcWe can drink a little, relax.
它是一个位时间。
It's been a while.
这拉多，一名男子abc与很多技巧。
OPHELIA: This is Lad o.abcHe is a man o f many ski II s.
作为一个园丁，只abc每天工作。
Gardening is just his dayj o b.
我要去冲个澡abc亲爱，你想我一起吗？
I'm going to go
take a shower, baby.
我很忙。abc目前还没有。
You want to come join me?
Absolutely.
Ah-ah. Not yet.
(DOORBELL CHIMES)
我可以帮助abc这家工厂他妈？
Baby, did you
order a fucking plant?
罗伯托・罗德里格斯希望退款。
Roberto Rodriguez
wants a refund.
Whoa, whoa.
听着...我是律师，abc我可以支付你所需要。
Look, you hire a lawyer,
you pay him, win or lose.
我们有一个协议，abc一个小古柯可以不值得这么多。
Roberto knew the deal.
That much coke?
There's no "get out
of jail free" card.
古柯，如果我们abc朋友没有异议。
So, instead,
you do all his coke
and miss all the motions and objections.
他们说，你可以有它。abc一起来看看。
You turn a five-year stretch into 20.
Mij o, take a look.
你偷了15年他生活。
He figures you owe him 15 years of his life.
好吧，我明白了，我们可以abc解决此问题。
Okay, I got it.abcI can still help the guy.
我们可以找到一个解决方案，abc我有很多钱，告诉我怎么样。
I got juice. I'll file
an appeal, all right?
我不想要你钱，我想abc确切地知道你多大年纪。
I got money.abcHow much does he need?abcName a price.
He doesn't want your money.abcHe wants your years.
42...
How old are you,
exactly?
我就开枪了你膝盖abc成为52，无论是62。
Forty-two. But what...
Roberto says to
shoot you in one knee,
make you 52.
- 给我我想要东西abc- 好了够了，拜托了
Both knees, 62.
Stop, please!
Sound fair, Mr. Lawyer?
给我一个该死abc机会说话。
Just give me
a fucking chance to talk.
I can help you, okay?
我可以帮你，好吗？
- 你怎么能帮助？abc- 如何呢？
How can you help me?
How?
我可以给你联系。
I can hook you up
with El Azul, that's how.
EL阿祖尔将与这件事情。
- 嗯，会...abc- 将赢得他。
Why would that
be good for me?
你知道这一切，abc这个交易。
Because he's
going to win.
Because you knowabcElena Sanchez can't cut the shit in this business.
阿祖尔一个重要人abc在墨西哥，
Azul knows
the turf in Mexico, man.
买警察，abc法官，政治家。
He's buying your cops, your judges.abcHe's political, man.
他会是快。
He's coming fast,
it won't be long.
你想获得董事会abc这列火车？
You want on his train?
我可以给你车票。
I can stamp your ticket.
我可以采取abc电话，你会在那里。
I pick up that phone,
and you're in.
去得到他。
Go ahead, pick it up.
好吧。
Okay. All right.
(DIALING)
-abc- 嘿。
(MAN GREETING IN SPANISH)
我乍得，告诉他，我有，
Hey, it's Chad.
Tell e I Jefe "Chip,"
though.
我现在跟他说话。
I need to talk
我有一个好消息。
to him right away.
I got good news.
所以它叫什么朋友，abc科摩本身骆驼吗？
So, pal, who do I say is calling?
(REPEATS IN SPANISH)
乔治基数较低。
George Lopez.
- 我们52abc- 操
Now you're 52.
先生，埃尔Azul。
Sen o r Azul.
- 这是什么？abc- 你想要什么？
(QUESTIONS IN SPANISH)
(SCREAMING)
告诉我，萨尔瓦多，Azul是到abc告诉你杀了罗伯特？
Tell me, was it El Azul who tell you
他妈白痴
to take a dive
at Roberto's trial?
好。
Fucking prick!
Buen o! Buen o!
这不是吗？没有答案吗？
Yes or no?
No!
我们到了62。
No answer? Now you're 62.
所有
EL AZUL: Buen o!
准备就绪。
H oI a!
高Azul拉多。
Azu I, it's Lad o.
- 操abc- 你还记得我吗？
Remember me?
狗娘养。
(CURSES IN SPANISH)
(SCREAMING)
北美在厨房里。
God damn it!
Oh, we're just making
gringo-lawyer soup
here in the kitchen.
拉多拉多
ESTEBAN: Lado? Lado?
(SCREAMS)
这是在做什么？
No!
Ya te metiste a I p o z oI er o cu I er o.
阿祖尔在蒂华纳有坏abc炸毁了一个仓库。
Azul, how was Tijuana?
Bad boy, bombing our warehouses.
海伦娜说，你需要abc一个更好律师。
Elena says you're
going to need a better
lawyer in the north.
你已经知道你需要做。退一万步，abc美好一天。
(YELLING IN SPANISH)
Watch the yelling.abcIt's bad for the blood pressure.
否
You have a nice day, too.
WOMAN: No! No!
- 做它。abc- 不
Do her!
No. No!
(WHISTLES)
不，请。
No, please!
- 你想他妈她吗？abc- 不
You want to fuck her?
号
No, per o...
如果你不希望是一个弱，abc你不能示弱。
If you don't, she'll be a witness.
And we don't leave any witnesses.
现在拉触发。时间。
Pull that trigger gently.
做到这一点
Now. Pull it!
(SNAPS PHOTO)
狗丹尼斯经纪人abc高品质药物。
OPHELIA: Dennis Cain is a high-I eve I drug enf o rcement agent.
没有这个人，本abc春业务。
With o ut this guy,abcBen and Ch o n w o u I d be o ut o f business.
愉快一天。
Nice day.
他们肯定是看到我在车里abc你在一起。
But I shouldn't
be seen in the same
zip code as you guys.
你喜欢我们进入到你abc办公室很多礼物吗？
Would you prefer we
come to your office
in San Diego with
your gift bag, Dennis?
安静水手。
Oh, take it easy, sailor.abcWhat's got your panties in a wad, now?
我们手在这个时候。
V俱乐部，从我想法，
A vid clip.
该标志已收集abc70斩首。
From, I think,
the Baja cartel,
我们讲敌人，
featuring seven
decapitations.
Talk about your hostile takeover.
- 为什么你叫我吗？abc- 来吧丹尼斯，发生了什么？
BC moving in on you guys?
Come on, Dennis.
What the fuck
is going on?
它发生，他们不是唯一abc白痴在这里交易。
What's going on is you're not the only
如果你想摆脱abc再往北。
indie frogs on the stove, my man.
They're killing each other down there in Mexico way.
如果你想摆脱更好地去abc火星。
And that's why they're moving north.
你说什么？
The forks are out, the pie's getting smaller.
太多话，一个单abc口，丹尼斯。
Why is that?
Too many cops
with their hands
in the pie, Dennis?
这只是...
That's just it.
我们要离开事情，abc是，但这个狗屎，
We used to keep the animals in the zoo,
- 伊拉克战争...abc- 什么意义呢？
but now, with this war on drugs,
it's like the war
in Iraq, Chon-boy.
因为在这笔交易中，我很感兴趣吗？abc他们卖了35万，去年？
Your point is what?
Why is it they
want our business
when they put out
35 million pounds
of grass last year?
因为他们在数量上。
Because your THC levels are off the fucking charts.
?30％吧？
They're like 30%, right?
- 33％。abc- 什么是他们吗？3?5？
Thirty-three.
Depends.
Yeah, and their
schwag is what?
Three to five?
来吧伙计们，他们是abc沃尔玛（Walmart）你本春。
Come on, man.abcThey're Wal-Mart, man, you're Ben and Chon.
他们希望有一个部分abc利润本及春。
They want a Ben and Chon section in aisle three.
因为它是如此很难理解吗？
Okay? What's so difficult to comprehend?
告诉谁不能来cagarci，abc在面对侵略我们土地。
Fine, tell them to
move their shit indoors
and buy their
own fucking lamps.
欢迎到经济衰退，其中一些abc有人们想要。
Well, welcome to the recession, boys.
You should be grateful
you still have
a product people want.
不是你偷偷溜走abc当他一部分吗？
So you don't mind if your envelope gets a little thinner, then?
伙计们，伙计们。
(CHUCKLES)
你知道我是廉洁营商abc你在一起。
You guys, you guys.
不存在任何问题，但目前还没有abc本春无丹尼斯。
You have a clean business, there's no problems.
But there ain't
no Ben and Chon
without Dennis.
所以，我始终是相同。
So, my envelope
stays the same.
这只是一个时间问题，
It's just a matter of time, guys,
前legalizzino这个狗屎。
before they
不要他妈与Wal-Mart。
Iegalize this shit.
Don't fuck
with Wal-Mart.
我选择，而不是条约abc斩首。
I'd take the deal
instead of decapitation.
继续渗透，abc甜美屁股加利福尼亚州。
You know?
Keep banging that
sweet California ass.
有没有什么好接受abc变化。
You guys had a good run, man.abcJust embrace the change.
以后见。
I'll see you.
丹尼斯，停止abc化疗？
Dennis, that new stuff
helping with the chemo?
这是...感谢人。
Yeah. Yeah, it is.
Thanks, Ben.
你会发送更多，你怎么样？
I'll send some more of that over.abcHow's she doing?
他快死了。
She's dying, you know?
你认为这仅仅是一个合适，男人。
(COCKS GUN)
Aw, man. I thought this was a business negotiation.
你有没有看过视频吗？
You saw the video.
这是在墨西哥。这是在拉古那。
Yeah, that was Mexico.
This is Laguna.
- 警方在这里骑自行车。abc- 那是因为我们认为逃生。
And cops here wear shorts and ride bicycles.
That's why we're
thinking of running.
静静本，不要停止。
You start running,
Ben, you never stop.
我们将一段时间，是温。
Now look,
we go away for a while.
It would be nice.
然而，还有其他abc赚钱方法。
Besides, there are other ways to make money.
不要将门，春
Don't get locked into one view of the world, Chon.
你知道，为了支付笔记本电脑abc儿童14美元？
What?
Did you know they're making $14 laptops for kids in Africa?
只有10元，可以abc改变这个世界。
What if you could make a $10 solar panel?
长大后本，abc你不能改变这个世界。
You'd change the world.
Grow up, Ben.
是你改变了。
You don't change the world.abcIt changes you.
VALET: Welcome
to the Bellevue, sir.
谢谢。
Thanks, I appreciate it.
来吧。
You're welcome.
- 我亚历克斯，他海梅，abc- 你好，早上好。
I'm Alex.
This is Jaime.
偏见。
H oI a.
Much o gust o.
让我们开门见山地说，abc我们业务。
ALEX: Let's get down
to business, shall we?
一切保持不变，abc你会保持不变。
Everything stays the same.
在这三年中，我们将abc您技术。
You're intact.
Over the three years, we'll study your techniques,
您生产方法。
y o ur pr o ducti o n meth o ds,
分布。
y o ur distributi o n.
如果它工作原理...交易abc增长极大。
I n return, y o ur business wi II gr o w immense I y.
我们分销abc国际
O ur distributi o n
is internati o na I.
我们会给你一个大型保护。
We'll give y o u pr o tecti o n
我们，我们abc价格
o n a sca I e y o u're
n o t accust o med t o.
兴趣并不太高。
We pr o vide Io w-c o st insurance,abcIo w-interest start-up Io ans,
服务洗钱abc生产商经销商。
m o ney-I aundering services t o a II y o ur pr o ducers and distribut o rs.
我们有大量abc在该国。
Y o u see, we I ease a g oo d am o unt o f I and in this c o untry.
一些是印度人。
S o me o f it,abcI ndian triba II and, n o t subject t o federa II aw.
除法律abc联邦，我们具有这样结构
负责种植。
We have the structure and labor force
- 数千英亩一次。abc- 在墨西哥字段是不一样。
to cultivate thousands and thousands of acres all at once.
Mexican field hands
do not grow primo.
我们将教你怎么做，abc你需要学习。
You will teach them this,
and they will learn.
我们看到您所有abc制药公司，
So you are the pharmaceutical company and the pharmacy.
- 预算？abc- 不完全是。
We're the botanists.
我们给予了很高价值abc我们科学家。
Not exactly.abcWe value our scientists and our seed-makers very much.
你想成为一部分，这些方法abc这个网络？
It is your methods
and your network
we want to partner with.
它一个合资企业，而不是一个党。
A joint venture.
No pun intended.
说得好。
Well said.
付款将采取abc份额分配。
In return, we take a modest distribution fee.
这将是...
Which would be?
20％
20%.
剩下80％，你自己。
80% is all yours.
而在过去3年？
And after the three years?
我们将增加音量。
We'll grow your volume.
利润在3年内将成为abc3540亿美元。
Your profits in three years will be 35 to 40 million.
3年后，我敢肯定，abc要协商赔偿。
After three years,abcI'm sure you'll be pleased
and quite willing to
re-negotiate our fee.
我们鼓励自主abc成为会员。
As we want to encourage
other independents to
join our association.
我们需要一个时刻。
We need a moment.
(CHATTER OVER RADIO)
莱利担心，电子，abc只有一件事：声音。
OPHELIA: Wi I ey is a t o p mixer.
本安全性及春。
He d o esn't care ab o ut anything but s o und and Ben and Ch o n's prim o.
亚历克斯，我们将发送abc开始一方。
CHON: I wi II say again,
Io ud and c I ear.
We send Alex and Jaime
back in a cereal box,
get this party started.
如果我们这样做，我们就会失去，abc我们不能
Vet o that.abcTw o errand b o ys, Ch o n.
They can rep I ace every man they Io se, and we can't.
医生，山姆比利前abc士兵在阿富汗，
OPHELIA: D o c, Sam, and Bi II y.
他们一起已经造成120人死亡，abc但他们是甜，当你知道他们。
Ex-SEALs fr o m Afghanistan.
T o gether, they've g o t ab o ut 120 ki II s.
在过去时间，如果你让abc人认为你是弱者，
Sweetest guys, when y o u get t o kn o w them.
CHON: Last time, Ben.
迟早你要杀死他们。
Y o u I et pe o p I e
think y o u're weak,
sooner or later
you're going to
have to kill them.
- 我们不同意朋友。abc- 难道我们不能。
Buddha would not agree.
What does a fat Jap know?
一个胖胖印度。
He's a fat Indian.
请你。
Whatever.
所以，你想我们业务。
So we dig you guys sound like Goldman Sachs,
这并没有引起我们关注。
but it's just
not our thing.
然后拒绝我们提议。
So, you are
rejecting our offer?
不
No.
我们将为您提供我们业务。
We're going to
有你一道去。
give you our business,
任何个人。
but we're not
going to join you.
Nothing personal.
没有个人
ALEX: N o thing pers o na I?
我相信，我们客户abc将作为他个人事情。
I'm afraid our
client would take this
very personally.
好了，我很抱歉。
BEN: Well, I am sorry.
我们拉了出来。
We want out of the dope business.abcIt's become a bit of a drag.
这很无聊。
- 我们想要东西不同。abc- 什么样事情？
We want to do
键入清洁能源可再生能源。
something different.
Such as?
Such as clean,
renewable energy.
你指是太阳，风abc狗屎一样？
You mean sun,
wind, ethanol?
Shit like that?
这是正确。
There you go.
你有什么说？
What do you have to say?
我？
Me?
Mmm-hmm.
在一般情况下，你要我吃abc你屎像鱼子酱。
I think, basically,
you want us
to eat your shit
and call it caviar.
(ALEX CHUCKLING)
- 这是什么好说呢？abc- 什么是外遇狗屎。
What'd he say?abcWhat'd he say?
(WHISPERING)
- 你犯了一个错误。abc- 好吧。
You're making a mistake.
我们为您提供24小时重新考虑。
Right.
We'll give you 24 hours to reconsider.
我们慷慨提议。
Well, in light of
our generous offer,
我们将讨论，
we would like to reconsider and think about this.
并认为你好意。
给我们48小时内，我们需要谈谈abc生产商经销商。
Give us 48 hours.
我们是独立思想家。
We need to talk to producers and distributors.
我们将谈论明天这个时候。
They're very
independent thinkers.
We'll talk tomorrow at this time.
Well...
他斯坦是一个代理abc投资银行。
OPHELIA: This is Spin.
He used t o be an investment br o ker f o r a big bank,
最近赚了很多钱，abc本春回收工作。
but then he f o und o ut he c o u I d make a Io t m o re m o ney
嘿怎么样了，人呢？
I aunderingabcBen and Ch o n's pr o fits.
Hey, what's up, guys?
How you doing?
银行没有感觉将被错过。
The bank didn't miss him.
我们把你东西。
Got a little something.
草
Shit. Sweet.
(SNIFFS)
我们必须隐藏了一段时间。
We need to get off
the grid for a while.
- 复地。abc- 这不是强。
Cool.
好吧。安妮
Yeah, no,
it's not really.
Okay. Uh, Annie?
我需要第一线，abc双重保护。
I need you to set
up a new line for us.
行吗？全部清除，清洁，abc循环一遍。
Double-blind,
all right?
Everything washed fresh, a whole new cycle.
我们可以去地方abc没有人会跟踪。
Make it go away somewhere for a while so no one can trace us.
你在开玩笑吧？需要多少时间？
What, are you kidding me?
我不知道。技术研究abc至少2年。
How long?
I don't know.
Botanical research,
call it a sabbatical.
Up to a year.
明白了，没问题。有没有问题。
Huh.
一年或两年。
Grab a seat.
Okay, no problemo.
- 三。abc- 转至步骤3。
A year for two of you.
Three.
Three? Who's three?
好吧。
O.
3人，其中包括abc死啊，他们要消失。
(TYPING)
Okay, three people.
One of them is O.
12个月...家，餐饮及娱乐。
So, that's a whole new
clothing line of its own.
Twelve months.
Housing, meals,
entertainment.
什么地方你觉得呢？
Where are you thinking?
印尼。
Indonesia.
- 在印尼到底在哪里？abc- 我们不能说。
Where in Indonesia?
Can't say.
如果我来了严刑拷打。
In case you get tortured.
有什么好玩。
Joy.
这件事严重吧？
You guys are serious, huh?
好了，你会需要直接访问abc到一个电子邮件帐户。
All right, well, you're going to want easy access to a mil, anyway.
屁股，我让他去abc心甘情愿一个骑我自行车。
That girl's ass...abcShe could ride my bike anytime.
您可以集中精力上数字吗？
Can you focus on the numbers?
我不问另一位朋友。
Hey, I'm multitasking, pal.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
我知道你会做abc跳过协议。
I knew you wouldn't make the deal.
我们认为这是离开时候了。
We think it's time
to get out.
不是永远，也许一年或两年。
Not forever,
maybe a year or so.
什么时候，你会去吗？
When are you going?
明天晚上，我们abc小时计算。
Tomorrow night.
They got a clock on us.
在哪里？
Where?
印尼。
Indonesia.
你看，我安装下水道系统abc在一个小村庄。
I put a water system in this pretty little village, by a beach.
在海滩上，人们生活abc更多甜食，你可能会遇到。
And they're
the sweetest people
you'd ever meet.
- 我想你一定会喜欢。abc- 我也一样。
I think you'll love it.
Me, too.
- 什么？abc- 好吧，我不能想象没有你。
What?
Well, I can't imagine
it without you.
我们只有3我们。
It's the three of us now, O.
噢，我上帝
(LAUGHING) Oh, my gosh!
它？
Yeah.
在印尼？它类型abc10千岛群岛还是什么？
Where in Indonesia?abcIsn't it 10,000 islands or something?
- 嘿，你有护照吗？abc- 有效吗？
Here, you got a passport?
- 他做我妈妈好吗？abc- 告诉她，只有几个星期。
A valid passport?
My mom's got it, okay?
- 后...abc- 是，你已经得到了它。
Tell her just for a few weeks, and then...
我们已经准备好了。
Yeah, I got it.
我们会喜欢那部电影。
Then we'll re-adjust
the clock from there.
- 阿凡达abc- 仙境。
We're like that movie.
Avatar?
来吧，与保罗・纽曼（Paul Newman），abc，你知道，当他还活着。
What movie?
You know, the one with Paul Newman when he was, you know, alive.
E...
And Robert Redford, when he was a total babe.
当他是罗伯特・雷德福abc冷却恐惧。
啊，神枪手与智多星。
Butch Cassidy and
它我喜欢女孩。
the Sundance Kid.
我不这么认为。
I'm like, the girl.
- 你abc- 但不会死到底是什么？
Wait, don't they
好了，不是女孩
get killed at the end?
Not the girl.
(DISHES CLATTER)
Get down!
(LAUGHS)
- 哦，我上帝你呢？abc- 一个小nervosetti，不是吗？
Oh, my God.
A little jumpy,
are we?
绿灯？
You think?
Are we clear?
怎么样，如果我清单abc我们特色甜点？
So, how about I tell you folks about our dessert specials?
因为，不是吗？
Why not?
All right, first off, we have a delicious creme brulee.
It's got a thick sugar coating, going to break like glass.
(CHEERING)
Feet are too close, Frankie!
Spread them. Follow through.
Where's the change-up?
哪个该死吸收？
I can see it coming.
Watch your feet.
我不知道所有白色他们喜欢人。
Keep them guessing!
也许他们是FAGS。
也许，如果让他们两个。
How much are we paying his goddamn pitching coach?
Two thousand dollars
and the kid can't even
get his stance right.
野兽。
Look at the
other one up there,
half asleep.
好吧。
(YAWNING)
你准备好了么？这种新东西。
Junior! Wake up!
有没有尝试过abc像这个。
I'm talking.abcDon't make me come out there!
Okay.
LADO: Are the kids coming home for dinner?
Angela's going to the Cheesecake Factory with Courtney and Taylor.
It's Friday.
LADO: The Cheesecake Factory.
In Mexico,abcI picked my meals out of the garbage truck.
That's why our children are Californian now.
That was the idea,
Miguel, wasn't it?
Maybe we should go
and visit more often.
So Courtney was all like,
"I'm so over it."
And I was like, "No, bitch, you're so not 'so over it."'
Look at your daughter.abcShe looks like a little whore.
Nice. About our daughter.
She's 15.
Don't come crying at me when she gets knocked up.
She's on the pill.
The pill.
You know what?abcThat's like telling her, "Go ahead and fuck."
You know what?
We should sit down
at the table,
the whole goddamned family, 'cause I can see what's happening.
(JAUNTY MUSIC PLAYING)
Hello.
I'm on my way.
Who was that?
(SIGHS) Don't start.
Mmm?
Where are you going?
I gotta work.
Take the kids
out to dinner.
Okay? I'll be late.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
Don't insult me
in front of everyone.
What are you, crazy?
Do me a favor.
Next time you come home in the middle of the night,
take a shower and wash her stink off, will you?
Nice Latina mouth you got lately, Dolores.
You think you left the old ways behind?
Well, let me tell you something.
Tijuana is coming here.
It's chasing us.
- 你找到了我针吗？abc- 为什么太小了。
- 你喝醉了吗？abc- 海伦娜。
- 你忘了你电话访问。abc- 对不起，对不起，你知道...
(CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
这是怎么回事？
如果它们fustacchioniabc这样做红鱼。
现在我房子。
So, which cock
does she suck?
已经在两个小时。
I can't tell.
The white guys
like each other.
妓女？
不，她是一个富家女abc或类似东西。
Maybe they're faggots.
Maybe she
does them both.
E没有人abc或吃狗屎鱼子酱吗？
Savages.
很难说。
有趣是，如果他们两者都做？
All right. Are you ready?
我知道你不想让我告诉你，abc干妈。
This is the new stuff.abcYou've never had anything like this before.
但我认为逃脱。
我可以进去abc并改变他想法。
Oh, man.
没有熊。
我需要他们知识abc技能。
有趣人，美国人。
我想我找到他们弱点。
It's good.
- 这是美丽？abc- 不错，但
您有一种风格更好教母。
It's all right.
我已经老了。
当我们抵达印尼，
我意思是，如果事事不顺心。
如果你所在位置。
会发生什么事？
你去哪里？
我要回家了吗？
我...
我不想错过。
我爱你。
因为你是我唯一亲人。
我可以停留长达3个月abc在印度尼西亚。
我不能永远。
移动到丛林似乎abc强，但
这将是卫生纸？
所以这么多水，abc不用担心。
到这里来。
来吧，不要去印尼，
(SINGING IN SPANISH)
让我们永远呆在这里，abc就在这里。
我们可能会隐藏在这个房间里。
- 我从来没有...死...abc- 有永远也找不到它。
(PHONE RINGING)
- 这是不可想像。abc- 没有，我们没事了。
LADO: I can't find my prick here.
That's because it's
too fucking small.
What are you, drunk?
我意思是说，我很想念这个地方吗？abc它。我喜欢这里。
E I ena.
You left the phone on.
但我可以很容易地说，abc再见，继续前进。
N o, I'm s o rry, I'm s o rry.abcY o u kn o w, I'm just...
因为它是如此容易？
(ZIPS PANTS)
What's g o ing o n there?
因为有更多美丽，abc美丽不是住在这里。
(URINATING)abcThe u r o s got drunk with a b o nita.
They all went inside their house.
They've been there now for two hours.
埃斯特...打电话给梁咏琪。
A wh o re?
No, she's like a rich girl or something.
She belong to
"Nothing personal"
or "Eat-shit-caviar"?
这是今晚非常激烈。
Hard to tell.
Interesting.
Are they sharing?
与所有abc我们抽烟，喝酒。
I kn o w y o u d o n't want t o hear this,abcMadrina,
but I think they're g o ing t o run.
我们必须做更多常。
I could walk in
there right now
and take them,
ta I k t o them o n y o ur beha I f.
No, Big Bear.
I need their network
and their expertise.
嘿，
你感觉怎么样？
I nteresting pe o p I e,
Americans.
好。
I think I found
their weakness.
先生们。
Is she pretty?
- 谢谢你到来，伙计们。abc- 没问题。
Yeah, she's pretty, but y o u g o t a better-loo king sty I e, Madrina.
I'm getting old.
- 我参加最后一件事情。abc- 嘿。
我们明确吗？
When we get to Indonesia,
更多开道。
I mean, if things heat up, if they find you,
6点宵禁，灯灭abc在午夜
- 这是爸爸。abc- 请不要忘记你护照。
then what happens?
Would you guys
have to go?
我爱你们。
Would I go home?
I don't...
I don't want to lose you guys.
I love you.
Because you're
my only family.
I've got three months tops in Indonesia.
Oh, no.
I can't lock down there.
OPHELIA: Living in a jungle sounds great,
我母亲是某处abc在世界上与她已故丈夫。
but where's
the toilet paper?
(BOTH LAUGH)
我这样想参与abc该计划教皇月。
That is, by far,
the least of your worries.
And the Chanel?
I know.
所以我写在卡片上abc我在欧洲，连续4周
Come here.
我最好朋友，露西。
学习有点文化。
Let's not go to Indonesia.abcLet's just stay here forever.
听杰克，试想一下，它就像一个阶梯abc经济，好吗？
墨西哥人做业务，但你abc他们将是一个合作者。
Right here.
标志利润，abc新日历。
We can just hide
in this room.
你会赚更多钱，比我见过abc我们用。
BEN: I cannot die in
fucking Laguna.
They won't find us.
世事无常，不要放弃。是abc如合作社，不会持续太久。
No, not in Laguna.abcWe're wherever we want to be right now.
同时积极回报一年。
特拉维斯数字消失abcOK，因为我们说话吗？
I mean,abcI'll miss this place, sure.abcI love this place.
你，我删除网格，把abc一个病毒cracco好。
But I can say goodbye and just move on.
不，不跟着你，安静。
Why is it so easy for you?
Because there
are better things.
迪克偏执，abc它让你疯狂。
There are better things than what's here.
(SPEAKS IN SPANISH)
That was pretty intense last night.
Maybe we ought to stop smoking that strain.
Or make
a lot more of it.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Hey, how are you feeling?
Good.
Gentlemen.
Thanks for coming, guys.
Sure.
Five minutes.
知道，因为我停止先生吗？
(SNIFFLES)
让我猜猜。
I got to make my final pilgrimage to the mall.
这里...
Hey, I'm sendingabcFrankie with you, okay?
If Frankie can keep up.
6:00 p.m. curfew.abcThe flight's at midnight.
Yes, Daddy.
Please don't
forget your passport.
I love you guys.
OPHELIA: My m o m was o ff s o mewhere in the w o r I d with her I atest husband.
I I ike t o thinkabcI'm in the midd I e o f a 12-stepdad pr o gram.
S o, I I eft a n o te saying I'd g o ne t oabcEur o pe f o r f o ur weeks
with my best friend, Lucy,
t o get s o me cu I ture.
Look, Jake, think of it as economy of scale.abcAll right?
The Mexicans will do business, but you'll be a corporation.
They'll assign your profits and your timetables
and you'll make more money than you ever made with us.
Things change, don't give it up.
They're like corporations.abcNone of them last.
Besides, we could be back running the show in a year.
Travis, phone numbers are vanishing as we speak, okay?
任用星期一，abc上周三，我会回来给你。
Yes, I'm wiping the grid.
I'm putting a little virus in there to fuck them up.
- 我很想念你亲爱。abc- 是，我也想你。
No, they're not going
to chase you. Trust me.
但我希望你能有abc来了，一个周末。
Fucking hell.abcParanoid as fuck.abcHe should lay off the Kush.
好吧，我答应尽快abc学期结束时，我是来寻找。
- 但有更多东西。abc- 你想我没有好成绩吗？
过程。
你不希望它结束在蒂华纳abc迭戈追我。
你马玛塔？abc难道你不来看看。
你知道，我可以向他们发送。
那些可怜人是一个人在这儿。
- 因为你不卖呢？值得一财富。abc- 你在开玩笑吧他妈？
(SIREN CHIRPS)
我如何出售他们，如果你爱他们吗？
来吧，告诉我，谁格雷格说？abc你怎么样？
我很遗憾地告诉你，abc格雷格水大桥下。
而这发生了什么？时代abc所以可爱。
你知道吗，我要结婚abc18年或19年，不用担心好吗？
你知道莲娜。
我知道，我相信，只是不想abc你跟随我脚步好吗？
但不要忘了一秒钟。
Do you know why I
stopped you, sir?
我是唯一母亲，你有。
Let me guess.
我爱你。
You know what, man?
亚历克斯。
嗨，亚历克斯，你是在免提通话abc春在这里。
？
我们让他改变了主意，abc有。
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
我们很高兴听到这个消息，男子
还等什么？
继续进行作案手法吗？
约首先想到abc明天早上？
我会受到影响。
MAGDA: I'm just saying, Ma,
I got a Sosh midterm
on Monday and an Econ
paper due Wednesday.
(ELENA SPEAKING SPANISH)
ELENA: But I was h o ping that y o u c o u I d c o me f o r o ne weekend.
O f c o urse I d o.
You don't want me to end up in Tijuana with Diego chasing me, do you?
What ab o ut y o ur h o rses, Magda?abcY o u never c o me t o see them.
O
您好
您好。
MAGDA: Why d o n't y o u se II them?abcThey're w o rth a f o rtune.
对不起这么多了，亲爱。
Are you fucking kidding me?
你卖，我保证。
Que pas o?abcHe was such a nice guy.
MAGDA: I n America, y o u d o n't get married at 18 o r 19, M o m.
S o y o u can re I ax, o kay?
(ELENA SPEAKING SPANISH)
ELENA: I kn o w that, and trust me,
I d o n o t want y o u t o f ollo w in my f oo tsteps at a II.
But don't you forget for one second
哪一个你先生abc没有什么人吗？
that I am the only mother you'll ever have.
- 这是我。abc- 如果你触摸它...
I love you.
别吵，别吵，我们可以感受到abc对付它。
我们提供了一个协议，abc然后听你建议。
(MOTORCYCLE REVVING)
我们有一个协议abc你被要求要尊重它。
你撒了谎。
我们将做任何事情。
如果您计划改变abc态度 -
你证明这一点。
(PHONE RINGING)
- 这不是一个问题。abc- 真吗？因为第一状态。
This is A I ex.
So, hey, Alex,
you're on speaker.
Chon's next to me.
现在，事实并非如此。
And?
现在，让我们这样说话abc先生，狗屎吃鱼子酱。
We changed our minds.
We're coming aboard.
我在这里。
Hmm.
我挑战。
We're happy t o hear that.
对不起。
So...
不，你不是。
Look, we want to
拿起你枪。
go over the MO.
How about first thing tomorrow morning?
站在照相机前面abc我在哪里可以看到。
We'll get back t o y o u.
(LINE DISCONNECTS)
现在ficcatela中，abc嘴狗屎。
把两个手指。
我做。
现在休息，你手指放在扳机。
(JAUNTY MUSIC PLAYING)
神圣上帝听着，abc必须有一个更好办法。
不，不要春
费尔莫。
您现在可以把它关闭。
好吧。
当您下一次abc问什么，
不希望听到
(OPHELIA PANTING)
没有吃那些事abc鱼子酱。
O?
是清楚了吗？
Hi.
它。
好。
BEN: I'm so sorry
你给136英镑查看。
about this, baby.
We're going to get
you out, I promise.
在5小时内，否则收到abc电子邮件，你也不会忘记。
(JAUNTY MUSIC PLAYING)
5小时，现在开始。
我们必须继续...我们必须去。
Which one of you
(VOICE DISTORTED) is Mr."N o thing Pers o na I"?
I'm here.
If you fucking...
Shut up, shut up.
All right, look,
we can negotiate.
We didn't make y o u an o ffer t o hear a c o unter o ffer.
这种你床。
We made you a deal to which we expected compliance.
这厕所。
You lied to us.
您接收器。
We'll do whatever you want.
牙膏。
I f that affects a change in attitude,
梳子。
y o u'll have t o pr o ve it.
水。
That's not a problem.
Really? Because it
was a problem before.
- 明天早上见。abc- 没有牙刷吗？
It's not now.
G oo d.
N o w I et me speak t oabcMr."Eat-Shit-Caviar."
想用我手指？
I'm here.
You insulted me.
I'm s o rry.
No, you're not.
Take o ut y o ur gun.
- 你有吗？abc- 这是准备好了。
我们不发送经常136磅。
Stand in front of the camera where I can see you.
我们让干。
只有17或18磅。
Now stick it in that vulgar mouth of yours.
正在加载所有abc现在。
你呢？还是他们？
明天你就知道。
Cut off two fingers.
(OPHELIA PLEADING)
干得好。
I'm doing it! I'm doing it.
保持冷静。
(SOBBING)
Now put your finger on the trigger.
Look, there's got to be a better way!
本放缓。
No, God damn it!
What are you doing?
引导仿佛一切都很好。
Stop.
You may take it out now.
45分钟。
The next time we ask y o u t o d o s o mething,
即将出版。
I don't want to hear,
"Eat-shit-caviar."
我们有七分钟时间。
Am I c I ear?
G oo d.
Yes.
哦，妈。
You will make a delivery to us, in Chula Vista, of 300 pounds.
Y o u have five h o urs.
他妈。
O r y o u wi II receive an e-mai I y o u wi II n o t I ike.
引导安静，本。
Five hours begin now.
- 136磅：我们都死了。abc- 不，男人。
- 他死了。abc- 你疯了吗？
We gotta move.
- 你不能拍一个警察。abc- 你喜欢在你头上了一个大洞吗？
但是，不要死。
- OK，OK。忘了它。abc- 算了吧。
请继续直行。abc不要停下来。
不要老是说你夜晚abc死了。
春开枪打你，我说废话。
That's your bed.
- 嘿... 我们出路abc- 哦，上帝
我很紧张。
That's your toilet.
And that's your sink.
妈
You've got toothpaste.
A comb.
Water.
See you in the morning.
No toothbrush?
Do you want to use
my finger?
好极了。
两分钟。
You got it?
我们正拭目以待。
Everything's ready to go.
My boys had to go all the way to Santa Barbara to get you 300.
- 这是？abc- 2次盖帽。
Nearly wiped us out.abcOnly 30 or 40 pounds left.
搜索一家鱼店。
- 好吧，我看看吧abc- 店后面一个停车场。
So, who am I working for now? You?
右转。
Or them?
You'll know tomorrow.
公园他们。
We owe you, Eric.
Stay safe.
- 我应该关掉引擎呢？abc不 -
他们都来了。您abc安静。
CHON: Slow down, man.
Cops are like bees
all over.
来吧
We have 45 minutes.
什么是错，有人abc跟踪我们？
It's the next exit.
这个女孩会死缓慢。
We got seven minutes.
Oh, shit.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Fuck.
Drive real cool, Ben.
Three hundred pounds.
We're dead, man.
No, man.
He's dead.
Are you fucking crazy?
You can't shoot a cop, Chon.
Put one big thought in your head.
O is not going to die.
Forget everything else.
Oh, God, please,
Mr. State Trooper,
don't pull us over.
It's not your night
to die.
Chon's gonna shoot you,
I'm not gonna lie.
喝吧。
Hey, this is our exit.
Oh, God.
I'm pulling off.
(SIREN WAILS)
Shit!
他们付出一切。
Shit.
它？
我很高兴你正在学习abc所有合作。
Hard right.
你想我们吗？
同样事情，我们已经说。
- 3年，除..abc- 现在，你母狗儿子，17:30
Two minutes, man.
They're watching us.
- 这是疯狂。abc- 首付款，你有。
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
- E O？abc- 奥菲莉亚要去路程了一年，
Yes?
MAN: G o tw o b Io cks.
- 1年？abc- 我们会找到她，好吗？
L oo k f o r a fish st o re.
后可以回家。
Okay, I see it.
There's an a II ey behind the st o re.
如果有人将尊重abc协会公约，
H oo k a right.
女孩会死在一个残酷方式。
Put it int o park.
年。
事实上，我们做三个星期。
Should I shut the engine off?
N o.
如果我们提供钱吗？
Here they come.abcStay cool.
- 现在。abc- 杀了。
- 不，什么他妈你在说什么？abc- 如果我们做了这样废话，
当你得到什么，abc想要什么，他们会杀了你我们，
(ORDERING IN SPANISH)
我们有一个为期三年协议。
出来后一个。
- 他们要是钱。abc- 你不知道你在说什么。
If anything goes wrong,
if anybody follows us,
- 不给我们任何回报。abc- 他们将支付许可。
the girl dies slow.
- 不是吗？abc- 野兽是不是协议。
它业务，春，考虑一下吧。
- 我们是智取他们。abc- 这部分...
每个人在他生活中人们失望了。abc她，因为我们在拉屎。
当我说：杀了他们，太abc危险：你说没有。
让我们来谈谈：你将如何解决这个问题？
- 你会如何？abc- 你只是想要把他们全部杀死？
我还没有看到一个abc枪公鸡在她嘴，奔
我从来没有讨厌人abc所以在我生活中。
你觉得我会吗？
(SNAPS PHOTO)
布拉德很喜欢我...abc如果是真，我不知道，
但他说，我认为这是一个严重问题。
我很担心abc你是太难了。
你是什么意思？
Drink up.
不要让我笑...
这是不正确，
They paid in full.
因为我可以不说话abc谁是这里负责人吗？
(JAUNTY MUSIC PLAYS)
有人听到了吗？因为不abc我可以任何人说话吗？
Yes.
妈
ELENA: (DISTORTED) We're happy t o see y o u've I earned t o h o n o r y o ur partnership.
嘿我至少可以abc有一个干净房间吗？
沙拉，而不是abc通常比萨饼。
What do you want from us?
The same things we agreed up o n.
Three years. Except,
(NORMAL VOICE) n o w, m o therfuckers, it's 70-30.
(WHISPERS)abcThat's gotta be Elena.
The first payment y o u've received.
And O?
O phe I ia wi II be away f o r o ne year.
我不知道我母亲，abc但要知道，他们在这里学习。
One year!abcAll right, Chon...
要做事情真abc愚蠢。
At the end o f that year, she'll c o me h o me.
将其称为美国联邦调查局，或别人。
Fai I at any p o int t o meet the terms o f o ur partnership
因为我继父abcFBI，
and the gir I wi II die very bad I y.
或CIA，或一些abc这样。
(LINE DISCONNECTS)
我最好双方abc上网冲浪。
One year.
只简单地说，abc还好，只是...
O won't make three weeks.
What if we offer them cash?abcRight now?
所以，我可以告诉某人abc我很好，我还活着。
They're going to
kill her anyway.
Don't fucking say that.
They're going to make us jump through these fucking hoops
我知道你可以留在这儿，
until they get what they want.
Then they're going to kill her,
and then they're going to kill us.
Look, we made a three-year deal.
7天或10天。
She's out in one.
They want the money.
You don't know shit.abcYou're talking to Taliban.
Right. Okay.
They don't give back.
也许一个月。
All right.abcBut they paid for the dope.abcDidn't they?
Savages don't make deals, Ben.
无论你想要。
They're a business, Chon.
Think about it.
我可能是你女儿。
We're smarter than they are.
Yeah, in botany.
Every man in her fucking life has let her down.
She's in this shit because of us.
When I said, "Kill them."
"They can't come up north, there's too much heat on them."
You said, "No, let's talk about it." How's that working out for you?
That's your answer for everything!abcJust fucking kill everybody!
每周2次，abc而不是真正好人。
I didn't see you
stick a fucking gun
in your mouth, Ben!
I haven't left a man behind in my whole fucking life!
请走了。
Do you think I would?
你知道，睡眠没有奇迹，
我希望我有这种快感。
With Brad it was I ike...
- 丹尼斯，我们需要您文件上签字。abc- 什么？
I d o n't kn o w if this is
rea II y g o ing t o happen.
But with him,abcI fee II ike this is seri o us.
我说，不开玩笑abc那些人。
I think what w o rries me isabcI think y o u're t oo much f o r him.
我按照我意见，abc有一个愉快一天。
What d o y o u mean?
(LAUGHING)
I think y o u're t oo y o ung
丹尼斯留在车内或去abc圣地亚哥自己上司。
and he's just
a I itt I e bit oI der
and a I itt I e bit m o re demure.
你要解释为什么abc你50万美元，
I fee II ike the defining questi o n is, d o es he make y o u I augh?
当你说你有abc110万？
OPHELIA: This isn't fair.
Why can't I talk to whoever is in charge here?
不要告诉任何人，并不会消失abc我们有一个计划，每一种情况。
Huh?
怎么样在我们abcsullaiutarci回事？
I s any o ne I istening?
Why can't I ta I k t o any o ne?
我们互相支持，这abc这个故事发生呢？
Fuck!
(DOOR OPENS)
- 他们把O。abc- 真吗？
- 你感到惊讶吗？abc- 是。
Hey!
了乐趣，我们有孩子。
Maybe I could get
a clean room at least.
我不想让他们成长过程中没有abc一个母亲。
Maybe a salad every once in a while, instead of pizza all the time.
我们会从这里走。
听着，
当你进入这个领域，abc永远是干净，你知道吗？
(DOOR CLOSES)
要反对女王abc我告诉你，我看到那些人。
真是太可怕了，abc但在每一个社区
Y o u d o n't kn o w my m o m,
but if she d o esn't
hear fr o m me s oo n,
- 总有一个弱点abc- 她问题。
she's g o ing t o
你知不知道这样EL Azul人吗？
d o s o mething rea II y stupid.
这线人多年，abc现在出来。
She's pr o bab I y g o ing t o
今年有选举abc总统在墨西哥。
ca II the FB I o r s o mething.
他内线，她abc过度。
Because my stepdad,
he was in the FB I
有一个停止下abc大型种植园见过。
o r the C I A o r o ne o f them.
250000株，好吗？他一切。
正在失去男人金钱，abc作为一个石油泄漏。
S o y o u better get me
o n the I nternet s oo n.
这就是为什么回来abc像你这样男人。
Y o u can supervise me, sure.
That's fine.
But that way, at I eastabcI can te II s o me o ne s o mewhere that I'm a I ive.
- 她吗？他有房子吗？abc- E在蒂华纳。
甚至不认为，有更多男人abc整个美国大使馆。
And I kn o w that
I can be here
好吧，我意思是...
丈夫弟弟死了，abc两个孩子，死了。
f o r I ike seven t o 10 days.
我认为他有一个儿子，abc有男朋友了。
他女儿莲娜，死abc她，
- 这是我所知道。不是废话abc- 这是废话
A month, maybe.
- 我们要姓名，事实，应有尽有abc- 这不是合同一部分。
Wh o ever y o u are,
just think
- 现在你。abc- 不工作，到1940年
I c o u I d be y o ur daughter.
他们数据库保护abc防火墙他妈。
- 废话abc- 狗屎
我们可以abc刺，可以做
有没有更多时间，丹尼斯，abc我们现在必须做事情。
你知道吗？你他妈。
两个打破我球abc你他妈
我要走了
Twice in one week.
Not good, guys.
他妈
怎么回事？
Get in, please.
他们把O。abc我们O.
同时，我们将尽一切abc把她接回来，你明白吗？
You know, a little sleep can do wonders.
妈，春
To what do I
你打一个联邦特工
owe this pleasure?
- 哦，上帝abc- 法罗更比。
Dennis, we need your
files on the Baja cartel.
好了，好了，够了，够了。
What?
I told you, don't fuck with these people.
And I follow my own advice.abcHave a nice day.
我知道，我知道。只是...
你这狗娘养。
BEN: Dennis, you step
out that car, I'm coming
down to San Diego
to introduce myself to your district supervisor.
And you're going
to have a hard time
我想听到你丹尼斯。
explaining half-a-million dollars parked in the Cook Islands
when you clear 110,
after taxes.
妈
And don't even think about calling someone and having us disappear
because I got plenty of evidence in other people's hands.
So what happened
to our mutually-assured
destruction thing?
We rat each other out,
we all end up
in the same prison cell.
What happened to that?
They lifted O.
Really?
Are you surprised?
Yeah.
Well, I'll do time, but you got kids, Dennis.
They're already growing up without a mom.
You don't have
a move, here.
然后：
Now, listen.
很抱歉，如果食品是不是abc根据自己喜好。
When Hillary Clinton grows up, she wants to be Elena Sanchez.
You run up against "La Reina" Elena
and I'm telling you,
I see dead people.
That's really dramatic.
But in the reality-based community, there's always a weakness.
他们担心，你知道吗？
Okay, here's the deal.abcDo you know this El Azul guy?
All right. He was her
inside man for years,
and now he's out.
This year, there's the Mexican presidential election.
He's in, she's done.
There was a bust in Baja,
the largest grow ever.
A quarter of a million plants.abcIt's hers.
She's losing men, she's losing money like a BP oil spill.
That's why she's coming up and moving in on indie guys like you.
你好，亲爱。
好吧。我需要60天，
在本文中，并在所有abc这些地方。
Where does she live?
She got a house up here?
Tijuana. And don't even think about it.
你能吗？
She's got security, like, beyond the American fucking embassy.
- 当然。abc- 确定。
Look, this is the deal.
Husband, brothers, dead.abcTwo sons, dead.
She's got a son in Mexico City.abcHe's some playboy, he's alive.
A daughter, Magda, also dead.
And that's all
I fucking know!
This is fucking bullshit!
We need what the DEA's got on the cartel.
Names, histories,
stash houses.
手怎么样？
But that ain't part of the deal, buddy boy!
It is now.
It don't work that way.abcIt's fucking 1984 in there, man.
在一切顺利。
Their databases are encrypted in redundant firewalls.
准备好了。
Again. More fucking bullshit!
It's not bullshit!
Our guys help set up those firewalls.abcAnything can be hacked!
We're running out of time, Dennis.abcYou have to step up right now.
基督，更加比abc我从来没有见过卡。
You know what?abcGet fucked, both of you.
检查纸张。
Fuck me, fuck you.
我还带了两个，
I'm out of here.
您丹尼斯是正确。
(SCREAMS)
What the fuck, Chon!
Motherfucker!
这种律师，亚历克斯，abc赢得80万美元。
BEN: What the hell
are you doing?
They took O.abcThey took our girl.
拿有属性abc无处不在：
And I will do anything, anything, to get her back.
Do you understand me?
- 在沙漠中，迈阿密，伦敦，任何地方。abc- 检查。
它具有所有文件。
Holy shit, Chon!
You fucking stabbed a federal agent!abcLook at this!
你认为丹尼斯abc照顾？
Oh, God.
观看NTFS分区。
I'll do more than that.
要下地狱噱头。
Okay, stop, stop, stop.
好了，克莱尔，你可以在互联网上搜索吗？
好主意。
I'll figure it out.abcI'll figure something out.
旋转钱，显示abc他银行帐户。
Crazy motherfucker.
嗯..让我们来看看
他回到家里取两abc万美元。
I want to hear from you soon, Dennis.
取决于如何快速abc移动黄金白银。
DENNIS: Fuck!
但自尊6天。
- 你是在开玩笑吧？abc- 这是所有吗？
毕竟这些年来。
去死吧。
我觉得被冒犯abc你不明白。
嘿，我不赚了一笔abc做这一切。
比方说，3或4万安全。
这取决于我们如何处理它。
So, we're hearing
the food here is
not good enough?
来吧。
必须有以百万计abc那些房子。
会像罗宾汉。
他他妈罗宾汉。
We're concerned,
you know.
我喜欢它
一对夫妇ID，我们在PC上abc玩与那些混蛋。
DEA AGENT: Paul Durth.
我们在这里有一些危险吗？
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
但我不能说什么abcAlex先生？
我不知道这一点。
Hello, sweetheart.
这些都是 10亿美元现金abc在交流女孩。
I need 60 days on this card
and all the geo-locations on this one.
我们都很开心。
Can you do that?
Of course.
Okay.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER CONTINUES)
- 桑切斯女士，你看，我说了实话。abc- 我也是。而我得到1500万美元。
- 15是太多了abc- 为什么？不认为他们值得吗？
- 不，这是值得。再次...abc- 因此增加，狗娘养。
好吧，让我们想想abc片刻，好吗？
How's the hand?
- 如何... 12？abc- 停止与我洽谈。
Don't bite it again.
CRAIG: Let's run them.
我们13，abc没有永远有效。我给你两个星期。
，其余约abc保持相同。右
Whoa.abcIt's a mudslide, off two lousy cards.
我同意他说法。
This dude's ahead of the curve.
What do you got?
继续。
I got it, too.abcYour boy Dennis came through.
所以，妈妈，我在这里我在伦敦
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON RADIO)
This lawyer dude,
Alex Reyes,
set her up with a 100,000-acre ranch in Humboldt County.
如果您看到我肖像abc挂在我房间，你会死。
Elena "La Reina"
has got property
all over the place.
经验，更多美丽abc我所有生活。
In La Jolla,
parts of Palm Desert,
apartments in Miami,
London, Zurich.
Check it out.
在这里我abc真很感谢我家。
There's gaps here.
This guy's
shrouding his sources.
You think oldabcDennis pulled a Nixon?
我希望你知道，abc我是多么爱你。
It's an NTFS partition.abcHe fucked up the master boot record.
Claire, can you google those houses again?
我想念你...
Whoever did this
is very good.
我希望能看到您到来。
Spin? Cash.
What can we clear in now?abcChon and my accounts?
O
Liquid?
You can't dump the house or you'll take a two-million lump to the head
and depends on how fast I can move the gold and silver,
but let's estimate six to eight.
埃斯特万
Are you kidding me?
That's all?
你忘了...
After all these years.
请让我谈谈abc一些，但不是他。不是他。
Wow. You've been
fucking me in the ass.
请，而不是他。
I'm insulted you only just realized that.
I didn't go all Bono all over Africa and Asia, buddy-buddy.
Let's say we're three to four million short
depending on what we can get them down.
在那里... 有没有钱。
Come here.
他们指望。
There's got to be millions sitting in these houses
2或3次，每次周abc送他们到墨西哥。
at one time or another.
It would be like
Robin Hood.
见那个角落？
A fucked-up Robin Hood.
路...桥...路。
I love it.
单向...abc没有出路。
A couple of lEDs and RPGs might come in handy.
- 神经？abc- 不
We could go real
Sunni on these bastards.
不，抢劫现金时间。
Um...
好。
Are we in any
sort of danger, here?
春。我喜欢它人。
- 做什么？abc- 杀人。
Did I not tell you everything goes throughabcMr. Alex?
看，本，abc有没有一键式取消。
退休时间。
N o t this.
，我 5种类型腿abc准备参加。
This is 10 mi II i o n cash,
straight up, f o r the gir I.
不我同意。
And we stay happy partners.
- 这是我想法。abc-
阿尔法第一位置。
明白了。
查理3位置。
Look, Ms. Sanchez,
I thought this through.
复制。
S o have I, and I put her va I ue at 15 mi II i o n.
That's too much.
一个公司，抢劫，本。
Why? You don't
think she's worth it?
N o, she's w o rth it.
We're small, compared to you.abcGr o w up, m o therfucker.
不
Give us a break, here.abcAll right?
How about 12?
Y o u must st o p trying t o neg o tiate with me.
Thirteen is o ur number, but this is n o t o pen-ended.
嘿。
I give y o u tw o weeks.
3辆卡车abc就在你身边。
收到，先生们。
The rest o f o ur dea I stays the same. Agreed?
愿真主与你同在。
Agreed.
第四车辆abc就在你身边。
Let's get going.
查理，我们还有abc前门。
我们得到了他。明白了。
OPHELIA: Dear M o m, d o n't freak when y o u see the bi II.
我在你身后，
保持平静，直到abc我做了一个明确信号。明白了吗？
Remember, it's a o ne-time-o n I y in Paris.
它。
Did y o u kn o w y o u can't even ask prices
时，在他们身后接近。
o r the sn oo ty sa I esgir I s w o n't loo k at y o u?
啊，这里是我们合作伙伴死了。
These French bitches, they eat a II the time and they're s o skinny!
现在呼吸。 3... 2... 1...
OPHELIA: S o, M o m, here I am in L o nd o n.
Y o u'd die if y o u saw the p o rtrait o f O phe I ia hanging in my r oo m.
他们想杀死我们。
I'm having the time o f my I ife,
but being here rea II y makes me appreciate h o me.
输出。
下了车
I h o pe y o u kn o w h o w much I Io ve y o u.
放下该死玻璃。
- 去你妈，混蛋。abc- 有一台收音机
I miss y o u.
I'll see y o u s oo n.
O.
你知道这是什么意思呢？
Esteban.
哇
You forgot this.
你就死定了，宝贝。
(WHISPERING) Please let me talk to someone.abcNot him, not him.
来吧他妈
Please, help me.
不，来吧，来吧
我们方法
逐渐远去
4... 3... 2...
CHON: There.
There's the money.
That's where they count it.
Two, three times a week, they head south to Mexico.
You see that curve?
Road, bridge, road.
给我吧abc。
One way in, no way out.
钱abc。
把它给我，把它给我吧
You nervous?
No. I hijack cash
shipments all the time.
退后。走开。
(LAUGHS)
Good.
你不知道我们是谁，该死abc我们卡特尔，混蛋。
Chon, I don't know
if I can do this.
你去把你球，abcviolenteremo你妻子
Do what?abcKill somebody.
Look, Ben. There's no
"undo" button here.
你孩子。
There's still time
for you to walk away.
I got five good
guys ready to go.
No. I'm in.
This was my idea.
Good.
BILLY: A I pha-O ne in p o siti o n.
Copy that.
DOC: Char I ie-Three in p o siti o n.
你还好吗？我要你去abc带钥匙土地。
Copy.
(FLICKS LIGHTER)
带钥匙。
They don't call it hijacking for nothing, Ben.
No.
GPS？看到了吗？Sbarazziamocene。
道格你没事吧你？
来吧。
Three b o gies
c o ming y o ur way.
杰克，你怎么样？
Copy that, gentlemen.
May Allah be with you.
- 拉过来。abc- 不
First b o gie, c o ming y o ur way.
你有没有听到广播，abc离我们并不遥远。
- 操。abc- 很抱歉，本。
我们应该采取什么样方向？abc哪一个？
Charlie, you got someone knocking on your front door.
我生病了，男人。我感觉病了。
DOC: We g o t it. C o py.
我们邻居，不到3英里（4.8公里）。
I got your back.
I want you to stay flat
until you get that
clear signal from me.
拉他妈
You understand?
Yeah.
- 哦，上帝abc- 快点。
DOC: Sec o nd vehic I e is ab o ut 200 meters behind it.
Third, ab o ut 300 t o 400.
来吧
Here's our dance partner.
回到正轨，本
明天这abc废话真要结束。
Now, breathe.
Three, two, one.
埃尔南多已听到了JJ说abc戴着口罩圣诞老人MUERTE。
他们身材高大，认为比2。
(MEN YELLING IN SPANISH)
- 埃尔南多。abc- 这是？
他们有多少？
5，也许6。
在3个点，几乎abc在相同时间。
Bulletproof fucking glass!
他们取消了GPS。
Fuck you, put o.
He's got a radio!
- 这是什么？abc- 一个爆炸装置制作工艺。
LED，伊拉克。
Do you know what this is?
爆炸时东西正在接近。
lraq？
你他妈
El Azul招募士兵，可能abc墨西哥军队工兵美国人。
Whoo!
你不知道。
Y o u see that baby b Io w, man?
- 埃尔南多。abc- 请告诉我。
埋葬这些人...abc或什么左边。
寄钱给他们家庭。
Let's go, let's go,
let's go!
DOC: C-team, m o ving in.
我们可以说，什么人吗？
Move, move, move!
不说废话了，没有。
Four... Three... Two...
法拉真生气了。
如果你不说什么，abc将从报纸知道。
关闭abc他妈了。我...
知道什么做与海伦娜。
让我来处理这个问题。
塞萨尔
(YELLING IN SPANISH)
强
- 多一点。abc- 你，夫人。
玛格达画了吗？abc。
不，干妈。
(ORDERING IN SPANISH)
马..我...我有一个...
Do you know who
the fuck we are?
什么？
We're the cartel, cabr o n.
我有这样女孩abc坚持她说话。
We'll blowtorch your balls.abcRape your wife.
And your kids.
我自己女儿abc我不想谈。
但是，这...这是。
(GRUNTING)
把它放在这里。
You good?
Yeah.
I need you to go over
there and grab my case.
Grab the case.
你有要求吗？
我想跟abc老板，请。
(FIRES GUN)
GPS.
If you see it,
get rid of it.
Doc, how we doing over there?abcYou clear?
哦。
Yeah, we're c I ear here.
- 我...abc， - 埃斯特万不提供您需求？
Good. Go, go.
Jesse, how are we?
You clear?
嗯...
不，不，确实如此。
BEN: Pull over.
对不起。
No, you saw the radio.
They're not far behind.
只是...
I fucked up.
Tell me, Ben.
我有注意力无法集中，...
Which life would
you trade for O's?
我...
Which one?
我只是希望，或许我可以...
Fucked up, man!abcWe fucked up, man.
可能abc我神经紧张了一点东西。
I think we got close
to three million cash.
We're still
three million short.
Pull over!
发疯了吗？
Oh, God!
什么问题吗？
Hurry up.
你是在你月经周期？
Let's go!
Get yourself together, Ben.
意思是...这整个事情abc杀...
Because tomorrow,
the shit's really
going to hit the fan.
我明白。
我能问多久abc你如何对待它，欧菲吗？
(BEN MOANING)
(BARKING)
从八年级。
你想知道有abc注意力无法集中？
Come on.
您父母知道
Where are the kids?
他不在乎。
Angela's still at practice.abcThe boys are sleeping over.
When the hell
are we going
to sit at the table
精细。
and have dinner
like a family?
我可以做任何事情。
Get me a beer.
被殴打收费abc炸药手榴弹。
使用设备abc炸药协调
What's the matter?
远程...
Are you unhappy again?
本。
你肯定是这个时候？
You still seeing
that therapist dyke?
他们希望看到你。
Three hundred bucks an hour.
先生没有什么个人。abc海滨城市。
Maybe I can fix
一个小时。abc独来。 （
your problem. No fee.
哦，上帝，
嘿。
I'll make you pregnant again.
记得很清楚。
直接看他们眼睛。有abc有一件事你必须记住。
一件事。
(GRUNTS)
如果我给一个该死，你O。
(DOGS BARKING)
我将介绍肩膀上。
检查呼吸。
I want a divorce.
You want a what?
A fucking divorce.
I don't want to be your wife anymore.
(CURSING IN SPANISH)
- 下午好。abc- 下午好。 GIA
What you're going
to get is another
kick in the belly.
Now shut the fuck up.
所以...
This is America, Miguel.
我们有一个问题。
I already talked to a lawyer.abcI know things.
- 你在哪里昨晚？abc- 在家里，因为？
Mmm-hmm.
到底是谁这个家伙吗？
Dolores.
一个朋友朋友。
One time, I tell you.
昨晚他们abc撞上我们车。
You talk to a lawyer again,
and I will take the
three kids to Mexico
我们埋葬我们七。
and you will never
什么？
see them again.
你消息？
You know that's the truth.
Fuck you!
啊，我们是很好，该死
I promise I will kill you.
你在这个行业多年abc我从来没有杀死任何人。
That's the Dolores
I'd like to fuck.
现在告诉我...abc7人死亡？
最后一件事，我们想要
Turn around.
No.
在哪里，不是吗？
(SOBBING)
他朋友... 在哪里？
你问我往独来。
(DOGS BARKING)
Get out.
Get out of here.
- 你有吗？abc- 是。
我是那种更好办法，只有。abc更好了。
Get out! Go!
(JAUNTY MUSIC PLAYING)
更多轻松应对abc与这样人。
Better be good.
不要去想它了，伙计。abc我们什么都没有做。
ALEX: Hernando heardabcGigi say they were wearingabcSanta Muerte masks.
也许你应该abc看你人。
- 我们了解他们。abc- 不管怎么说，让我们来解决它，好吗？
They were tall.
Thinks he saw two.
- 我想谈谈与O。abc- 是。
Hernando.
Yeah.
How many guys
you think did this?
证明我说，活着。我给你一个小时。abc我做一切，你提出要求。
At least five,
maybe six.
There's three locations.
Almost at the same time.
And they ditched
the GPS's.
我们将拭目以待。
What's this?
That's an improvised
explosive device. IED.
It's from Iraq.
The sand-niggers use them
to blow up u r o armor.
Iraq.
Who the fuck...
- 你觉得呢？abc- 我认为他说是实话。
El Azul's been
hiring ex-soldiers.
Probably Mexican
demolition guys
from the Yankee army.
它没有欺骗球。
You don't know that.
- 我不会是这样，我知道。abc- 这并不重要。
Hernando.
- 我们必须拿，拉多。abc- 亚历...
Bury them like men, what's left.
我要告诉在海伦娜abc我想，当我让你知道。
Money to their families.
What do we tell Elena?
我会打电话给你以后。
That we know shit.
Nothing.
She's going to get real upset if we don't tell her nothing
and reads about
it in the papers.
Oh, shut the fuck up.
I'm the one who knows Elena.
Let me handle it.
César!
(ORDERING IN SPANISH)
Si, Sen o ra.
(IN SPANISH)
No, Madrina.
But, I have a...
What?
I have this girl that keeps insisting to talk to you.
(SIGHS)
(CHUCKLES)
下一次abc只是问我，你想要什么。
My own daughter doesn't want to talk to me,
but this one does.
Put it on.
饮料，奥菲莉亚。
You have a request?
上床？
Yes, I'd I ike t o speak t o the man in charge, p I ease.
时间小睡一会儿。
Yes?
Oh, I'm...
Has Esteban n o t been pr o viding the essentia I s?
- 哦，是abc- Magdita
Um...
哦，你好，妈妈。
No, he did.
- 争取成为已晚。abc- 猜猜
I'm s o rry.
我在加州。
I'm just having s o me c o ncentrati o n pr o b I ems,
- 什么？abc- 嗯，你知道他们在说什么...
如果山不穆罕默德，abc穆罕默德在加利福尼亚州。
and I was h o ping
maybe I c o u I d get
- I决赛，妈妈。abc- 我下周去，就是这样。
a I itt I e s o mething
t o take the edge o ff.
你，当然。我猜。
"The edge off"?
我很兴奋abc想法，看到你，我女儿
What's the matter?abcIs it that time of the month?
我不认为这是一个好主意，干妈。abc可以妥协情况下，对不对？
I mean the stuff we're a II ki II ing each o ther o ver.
我希望看到马格达。
我需要确保您安全。abc难知道。
I see.
一切都解决了。
May I ask you how long have you been using, Ophelia?
什么他妈你看，伙计？
Since the eighth grade.
(LAUGHS)
And you're wondering why you're having concentration problems?
D o y o ur parents kn o w?
They didn't care.
给她东西，所以...abc我无法入睡
All right.
在6小时唤醒。
I can arrange something.
所以，多给我保持关注。
FEMALE NEWSCASTER:abcThree vehic I es sm oI dering fr o m what loo ks t o be
a c oo rdinated, r o cket-pr o pe II ed grenade attack
used in c oo rdinati o n with I EDs,
which stands f o r "impr o vised exp Io sive devices."
CHON: Ben.
(JAUNTY MUSIC PLAYING)
These are the same types o f exp Io sives used by the Ta I iban
against o ur tr oo ps in Afghanistan.
They sure don't waste time.
They want to see you.
没事。
I don't know, man.
Remember the drill.abcLook them right in the eyes.
There's only one
thing on your mind,
one thing.
It's, "Fuck you,
you've got O."
I've got your back.
And watch your breathing.
Afternoon.
Fellas.
Good afternoon, yeah.
So, we got a problem.
说，您好，我们必须去。
Where were you last night?
蒙住眼睛。
I was at home, why?
Who the fuck's this guy?
An amig o, amig o.
Three of our cars
were hit last night.
Seven of our men are soon to be buried.
What?
That was you guys?
I saw that on the news.
This is fucking great.
I've been in this business for years and never had a person killed.
And now you're telling me, what, seven people are dead?
This loss ain't cutting into our share of the take.
好了，埃斯特，好样
Where's the other one?
Huh?
Your other amig o,
where is he?
埃斯特
You asked me
to come alone.
Hmm?
You asked me
to come alone.
它没有工作，
ALEX: I did.
你太敏感了。
You did?
(TALKING IN SPANISH)
Don't even go there, man.abcWe had nothing to do with this.
Maybe you should
look at your own men.
Our people know better.
Whatever, man.abcFucking solve it, okay?
I want to talk to O.
Yeah?
Proof of life.
Like everyone else,
we work for incentives.
We'll see.
Hmm.
你待遇，欧菲？
你还好吗？
(EXHALES)
他很好。
我不跟你说话，拉多。abc我说是奥菲利亚。
What do you think?
I think he's telling the truth.
你还好吗？
They don't have the balls to rob us.
我很好。
I'm not so sure,
you know?
It doesn't matter.
We have to report this to Elena, Lado.
好。
Alex, I'll tell Elena when I want her to know.
丘乔，带来abc依赖，谢谢。
安帕罗，洗孔，abc你需要什么，请。
I'll call you later.
因此，拉多..
现在，我们，我你谈谈。
让我看看你眼睛。
你还好吗？
这是干妈。因为你问了吗？
我把悲伤，拉多
我要拿出来abcGringolandia找到了吗？
你没想到我会abc实现$ 300万
我人，死了
由于作出自己决定吗？abc负心他妈
我让你，混蛋我
(OPHELIA COUGHS)
不要忘了乳腺癌abc调养你，混蛋
Next time,
ask me for what you want.
我很抱歉，干妈。
E是我错abc不立刻告诉你。
Drink up, Ophelia.
我只是想告诉你
这些罪犯abc你偷了钱。
Time for your bath.
Bathtub time.
所以，请
让我跟他一起去。
你，但一个人会说abc任何东西，以阻止痛苦。
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
妈，拉多你更abc傻比它声音
在这两种，它唯一女孩。
Oh, fuck.
不会做任何事情，abc危及他生命。
但是，不要分散从abc我们问题更大，
ELENA: Magdita.
Yes?
Hi, Mom. Wow, it's late.
，EL AZUL。
Guess what?
为了这一点，渗透abc集团在北方，
I'm coming to California!
这是你控制之下。
What?
We II, y o u kn o w
what they say.
但如果你认为我是abc只有一个赔钱，
If the mountain doesn't come to Mohammed,abcMohammed comes to California.
你会看到一个惊喜
I've g o t my fina I s, M o m.
首先，这3个abc百万美元
I'm coming next week,
and that's what's final.
他们ripagherai你是，你也一样
Yeah, sure, I guess.
第二，我发现，abc鼠屎
I'm so excited to
see you, mijita!
LADO: I don't think that's
a good idea, Madrina.
生意阿祖尔。
Azul could take
advantage of this situation.
感觉到你，我会去寻找abc你妻子，你孩子，
ELENA: I want t o see Magda.
I have to
arrange your transport.
It's complicated.
你他妈母亲，abc如果有必要
I t's a I ready
been arranged.
(LINE DISCONNECTS)
What the fuck you
looking at, man?
现在你可以走了。
你还等什么呢？
我给你男人，abc亚历克斯新银行账户。
I gave her some shit,
so let her sleep.
存款12,260每晚分开。
Wake her up in six hours.
我给他旅游abc世界2倍，瞧，
Sophia will wash her.
亚历克斯现在有一个建筑在开普敦，abc销售类型不存在。
我孩子们知道abc未能找到另一个ISP
找到另一种方式。
(OPHELIA GASPS)
在一天结束时abc成为一个坏人。
- 通话记录吗？abc- 哦，是很多。
帐户，搞砸了，abc将需要一个月
找到了自己家伙。
- 是什么让你家伙？abc- 从什么时候开始这样问题？
来吧，人，标志，abc此crocefiggeranno。
It's okay.
所以，你应该是好失去abc委员会这份工作？
他们知道他们abc成为怀疑。
，但我不知道，abc拉多了已经他计划。
盐PRI，PAN下降。
Okay, sweetie-pie,
time to go.
- 他们会去选？abc- 不，我搞砸了。
Last looks.
海伦娜了 死了
但是，你有你双脚牢牢abc在美国，我喜欢
因为不riniziamo？
如果没有老，我们之间摩擦。
在这样生活..
一切都是可能。
Este.
住手举起手来
It didn't work out.
You're too sensitive.
没有人一样优雅abcEL Azul，我一直在说。
我会打电话给你。
等待
欢迎区域。
那么你想谈什么？
Have you been
treated well, Ophelia?
坐下。
自我们上次abc愉快交谈，
Are you all right?
我做我团-Tabc深入研究。
She's fine.
I'm not talking
to you, Lado.
I'm talking to Ophelia.
我成本了很多。
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Good.
是什么呢？
Chucho, take her to the guest house, please.
您告密者。
(IN SPANISH)
是谁？
我觉得你付出是亚历克斯・雷耶斯...
有点了。
So, Lado, now I'm talking to you.
Let me see your eyes.
你不相信我吗？带它到abc雅伊梅称，他会明白。
球控制。
Is everything all right?
Yes, Madrina.
Why you ask?
有很多转换银行。
看一看之日起abc转移，
You make me sad, Lado.
- 抢劫。abc- 拉多？我想要更多。
I have to come
to Gring oI andia
to find this out?
You thought I
wasn't going to notice
$3 million,
and seven of my men dead?
Since when do you take
decisions of your own...
(IN SPANISH)
I made you,
motherfucker. I did!
让我看看你手。
(CLEARS THROAT)
I'm very sorry, Madrina.
It was stupid of me not
to tell you right away.
微妙，因为那些孩子。
I just wanted to prove
to you that it was
this Cheech and Chong
who were stealing
your money.
我忙事情男人。
So, please.
Allow me to talk to them.
Yes, and men will say anything to stop the pain.
我能问你一件事吗？
Mierda, Lado. You're
stupider than you look!
你爱你姐姐吗？
These two kids,
all they care
about is their girl.
They wouldn't do anything to risk her life.
我有一个姐姐。
But it's distracting you
奥菲利娅是不是你妹妹吗？
from our bigger problem,
which is El Azul.
不
To the point that
he has infiltrated
himself into
the northern group,
那稚嫩小奴隶
which is under your control.
你现在可以走了。
But if you think
I'm the only one
who's going to
be losing money,
you're in for a surprise.
就像你说，按照钱。
First of all, those $3 million?
You're going to pay for it.abcYeah, you, too.
红皇后，我abc邀请出去吃晚饭。
Second of all, you're going to find me...
我感到孤单。
一旦我有一份工作。
仪表一家餐馆。
...that gave up our
stash house to Azul.
我去大学一个abc各占一半，但
Or else, I'm going to have to go after your wives, and your children...
然后我就走了，因为
机构让我abc疯了，我想
我想尝试abc实实在在事。
你知道，我想我是abc我生活，以及如何得到它...
You may go now.
你们美国人总是说？
你有没有想过abc真正关心你未来？
What are you waiting for?
这是有点搞笑，abc情况中，他们是。
你饭，奥菲莉亚？
OPHELIA: The Red Queen asked me t o dinner.abcI think she was Io ne I y.
I had a job for a while.abcI was a hostess at a restaurant.
好，谢谢你，
I went to community college for a semester and a half.
你是怎么进入周围？
But then I left,
because institutions
make me crazy.
如果你不介意问题。
And I thought,abcI don't know, I wanted to experience something real.
I figured I just wanted to drown in life.
我们可以说，我abc继承地方。
当他们杀害了我丈夫，abc我喜欢这么多，
And how I made it out, that would...
Do Americans
always talk this way?
我别无选择。
Have you ever really thought about your future?
为什么？你有孩子吗？
That's a little ironic, considering the situation I'm in.
我双胞胎被打死。
How are your
lamb chops, Ophelia?
所以，我专门abc我自己生存。
Good, thank you.
你谈好您孩子吗？
How did you get
into the business?
我儿子恨我，因为abc我删除了命令。
他们会杀了他。
If you don't mind
my asking, ma'am.
我女儿。
他是我感到羞愧。
You could say thatabcI inherited the position.
我很自豪abc她这一点。
When they killed my husband, whom I love very much,
对不起。
I had no choice.
为什么？
What, you don't have sons?
我不知道，我觉得abc对不起，我对你。
My twin sons were murdered.
So, I have devoted my life to my surviving children.
我希望活着。
这两种。
Do you still get to
talk to your kids?
你死了。
My son hates me, because I took his power away.
They would have killed him, too.
And my daughter,
我喜欢你聊天，欧菲。
she's ashamed of me.abcAnd I am proud of her for it.
但是，请记住，如果你是，
I'm sorry.
我不会麻烦abc刺穿喉咙都有。
Why?
但不everd把它们放在一起，abc是唯一一个谁不能做它。
I don't know.abcI guess I feel bad for you.
来吧
你真吹牛吗？
My hope is still alive.
有什么错abc与你故事，爱人。
Both of them.
也许爱你，
And yours is dead.
但从来没有多少他们彼此相爱，
机智不，你也有同感，不是吗？
I like talking
to you, Ophelia.
玛丽甜
But let me remind
you that if I had to,
I wouldn't have a problem cutting both their throats.
Well, you'll never
get them together.
I'm the only one
who can do that.
Come on.
Are you really
bragging about that?
There's something wrong with your love story, baby.
They may love you,
but they will never love you as much as they love each other.
Otherwise,
they wouldn't share you,
would they?
您了17电话EL阿祖尔
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
否
SPIN: I gave your boyabcAlex a new bank account in Saint Kitts.
- 睫毛为您服务abc- 不，拉多，没有
Separate deposits
of 120, 260, and 90.
I spin it around
the planet twice,
and v o i I a.
Alex Reyes now owns
a building in Cabo,
sells it to
a resident of Palau
who doesn't exist.
OPHELIA: My men knew they c o u I dn't pu II o ff an o ther heist.
- 是或不是？abc- 海伦娜
S o they f o und a different way.
By end of the day, he's definitely been one bad little puddy cat.
在上帝名义我求求你了
Phone records?
对于存储器中abc雷纳尔多，请
Yeah. Plenty of backup.abcThis account is so confusing,
it'll take a forensic
a month just to find
his own dick.
对于我孩子
要玛格达
So, what did
this guy do to you?
我求求你
When do you ask
questions like that?
Come on, man.abcThis is the Baja cartel.
They're probably
going to crucify
this guy for this.
听着。我发誓。
So, you don't mind
losing your
commission on the deal?
你妻子贝蒂娜abc小家伙们，我爱他们。
有保险。
如果你不告诉我我想要听到，abc我要他们在这里，
OPHELIA: They knew they needed t o get the suspici o n o ff themse I ves.
分尸，我打开，我死了abc在你面前流血。
But what they didn't kn o w is that Lad o
was a I ready making p I ans o f his o wn.
这不是吗？
(HORNS HONKING)
所以，什么你说什么？
它。
这是我。
告诉更多强。
是，真实。
(EL AZUL SPEAKING SPANISH)
你，我叫El Azul。它。
我谈到与El Azul混蛋。
这是我abc求你救我
把它放下。
现在我们知道，
你是对，干妈。
什么你要我做他吗？
本次招标先生abc没有任何个人。
必须完成什么，他开始。
让她坐。
你人取得了系列abc指控我人之一。
我们这样做是正义。
谁需要照顾一个人abc他家人，我尊重这一点。
我想给你一个更好死亡。
不过，这将是一个坏榜样。
LADO: Welcome to the barri o.
没有，没有，没有
So, what you
going to talk about?
我不喜欢这些尖叫声。
Sit down.
Well, after our last
pleasant chat,
哪一个？
I had my IT guys do
a little deep research.
不是吗？你做你自己。
This cost me
a lot of money.
女王说，你必须做。
- 赫勒拿，拜托了abc- 你可以看一下这个
What is it?
Your informant.
Who?
把它给我。
I think you guys are payingabcAlex Reyes way too much.
不是你，鱼子酱，abc我礼物给他。
Don't believe me?
Give this to Jaime,
he'll get it.
Unless he's in on it.
There's a lot there.abcBank accounts, transactions.
Take a look at
the deposit dates
and match them up
with the hijackings.
(IN SPANISH)
Let me see your hands.
Soft, like a woman's.
And he's fucking me with them.
(GIGGLES)
Let me ask you something.
Do you love your sister?
I don't have a sister.
我读了你Buddah东西。
Ophelia's not your sister?
根据达赖喇嘛，
No.
如果你在一个情况下，你可以abc防止进一步暴力行为，
第一个快速击命中。
You're cute, I ambi o s o.
You can go now.
亚历克斯抓住了人，本。
Like I said,
他被折磨abc杀了人。
follow the money.
我们一样。
丹尼斯说谎了有关这些文件。
亚历克斯是在那里。
他发誓拿，玛格达。
他女儿。
意味着必须abc还活着。
I need to talk to Elena.
- 丹尼斯知道。abc- 是。
(QUESTIONS IN SPANISH)
She told you,
whatever I need.
我们缺少300万美元。
这可能是一个问题。
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
我们需要到scucirloabc丹尼斯不知何故。
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(TV PLAYING)
查找替换它。
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
绑架她是什么意思。
O
- 好吗？abc- 。
好吧。
I'm sorry.
What I said the other night was stupid.
教皇，一个人abc见到你。
I can't sleep and I thought it'd be nice
- 谁？abc- 我不知道。
to have some company for a few minutes.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
我正走在附近，我看到了abc必须修剪花园。
我们希望看到一个abc示范。
You too?
I like to TiVo.
Especially in America.
我妻子通常abc这些东西都是可怕。
OPHELIA: She's going
for the wrong guy.
萨拉・安娜，去abc你房间。
That one is such a player.
- 但是，爸爸...abc- 教宗说去吧
You think?
Girl, you have been out of the game too long.
拉多来我家吗？
Trust me,
I know a player
when I see one.
你威胁我女儿吗？
You really believe
that these women
can convince themselves
难道你不觉得那个谁abc摄像头无处不在？
that they can
fall in love
with men like this?
我不在乎。
如果我想杀死你妻子abc你女儿，我放火烧房子。
我给你你那该死提示。
You know what you were saying the other night, about my men?
你找到他们了
Yeah.
I never had a dad.
而且我你手吗？
He left.
我切abc改变一个车轮。
I don't know,abcI guess this is my way of getting to know man.
- 改变车轮？abc- 。
I didn't know my father either.
更改轮abc一个看到了
But I only loved one man my whole life.
我们需要谈谈。
You were never
with anyone else?
有些混乱abc因为你做了什么。
No.
像什么？
You must really miss him.
关于你是如何知道abc关于这一点。
你在抽烟沉重东西不错。
你有什么朋友。
You see how I never laugh
and I never cry?
我给你买了签证
行吗？我保护了6年公鸡。
Well, that's because I haveabcBotox of the heart.
现在去拉屎，你有7abc墨西哥人死了，一个律师
一名炮手。我服了你abc更多比以往任何时候。
I thought just in the face.
别再问我，你看起来像一个女人。
I don't have Botox
on the face!
No?
No, I don't!
(LAUGHS)
I made you laugh.
丹尼斯，
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
我知道你信息。
是什么让你认为它是不EL阿祖尔？
Bitch.
- 因为我知道它是什么。abc- 你是什么意思？
Hello?
- 因为我现在他一起工作。abc- 什么？
如果你骗我一次，abc我就开枪打死你这混蛋。
I see.
由于工作与阿祖尔？
(SIGHS)
I'll call you right back.
难道你不告诉我呢？
What happened?
There's been a problem.
前两天。
(CALLING OUT IN SPANISH)
Chiquita is going to take you back to your room.
我没有太多回报，abc我生活。
No, Elena,
please tell me
what happened.
I'm sorry, Ophelia.
I told you this
might end badly.
我会比赛中，abc我会是你没用。
(SPEAKS SPANISH)
Elena, please.
Just tell me.
我没想到这abc伊拉克精神病患者会发疯。
听着，我没有abc从未背叛过，从来没有。
And remember
you're not a hostage
because of me,
我是你最好abc盟友，美不胜收。
you're a hostage
because of them.
你说什么abc小骗局？
- 你疯了吗？我该怎么使用？abc・痛风 - 丹尼斯。
我给他权利abc我留在平。
- 是或不是？abc- 不，不
不，好不好？不
不
这只是我你，你这样做？
(WHIP CRACKING)
你一定要相信我这个哥们。
我不想错过这一切。
(ALEX SCREAMING)
我有两个儿子公鸡，他妻子，黛安。
感谢丹尼斯，我abc两百万美元。
Elena! Stop it! Please!
我要那么多钱。
(MEN YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
这是我钱。abc我钱。
妈，你不能信任abc更多比任何人。他妈。
LADO: Lucky seven.
我不相信即使我妻子。
Did y o u make 17 ph o ne ca II s t o E I Azu I?
你知道，试图abc离婚了，你知道吗？
N o!
GIA。我妻子错过事会谈，abc以上中年危机朋友。
LADO: Ten I atigaz o s
to go, cabr o n.
ALEX: N o, Lad o, n o!
你怎么知道是谁abc相信谁呢？
我意思是，让我们去。
您已经给出了abc工作，你答应吗？
因为你知道，海伦娜abcCaschera，所以容易。
你知道，那3万abc他钱。
(SOBBING)
所以，不要愚蠢认为。
但是，你认为谁你愚弄了吗？
Yes or no?
Elena, in the name of God.
- 我该如何ridarai钱？abc- 货币...
I beg you!
您需要我，我再一次给abc你钱。
(IN SPANISH)
但是，他们需要女孩。abc男孩想这个女孩。
我爱是abc女孩，他妈。
这需要O，好吗？abc那么，是什么？
I beg you!
我不存在一
你意思是你没有吗？
在哪里？
Listen,
与海伦娜。
I promise you this.
在墨西哥？
Your wife,abcBettina, and your little ones that I like so much,
- 不，在这里。abc- 在这里吗？
E来到这个地方abc看到他女儿。
they will get the insurance.
另一位妇女告诉我，abc该怎么做，使我。
But you tell me
"no" one more time,
这种疯狂人。
I will drive them here
洛林海伦娜在美国本土？
and I will cut them open
我告诉你，土著人土地，abc保护它。
and make them bleed
to death in front of you.
你，我会采取修复它，abc在这里，因为你需要给丹尼斯。
Yes or no?
- 想想。abc- 不要告诉我想。
What's it going to be?
不，不，美丽，听着。abc这些人有300万。
什么你觉得会吗？abc给他们拿？
(IN SPANISH)
对吗？
Finally. Louder.
第一件事，卖出abc海伦娜女儿。
行吗？我们把钱分，abc给一个该死海伦娜。
操他
Louder!
明白了吗？
(BEGGING IN SPANISH)
LADO: Cut him down.
(RINGING)
LADO: Now we know.
丹尼斯要3万abc美元，孩子们要玛格达。
You were right, Madrina.
What d o y o u want
me t o d o with him?
丹尼斯像往常一样，abc向前迈出了一步。
The soft one.
唐氏那些他妈手。
Mr. "Nothing Personal."
他威胁我女儿，abc我女儿
He must finish what he started.
足够投诉。abc是你应得浑身疼痛，混蛋
- 你背叛了。abc- 如果我没有选择。
Sit her down.
你可以得到更多，abc做更多钱。
Your men have brought some serious accusations against one of my men.
- 但你想打脏。abc- 我们要玛格达。
我想你是聪明，而不是abc这里有两个傻子。嘿。
This is our way of justice.
你想控制所有abc奥兰治县海岸？
他妈她吗？
For the love of God!
- 什么？abc- 你生活。
- 我要得到你。abc- 好吧，反正我会是死...
A man takes
care of his family,
and I respect that.
但一想到知道如何监狱abc为你余生，
我会更多愉快生活。
I'd I ike t o give
y o u a better death.
数以百万计现金abc知道在哪里以及玛格达。
But it would
set a bad example.
告别你妻子，abc女孩消失。
三万元。
No, no, no!
或者没有交易，而这个abc我通输出。
I don't like the screaming.
出了什么事情？
Oh, God!
丹尼斯。
没有人要你。
Magda你唯一希望。
3万元，给予或采取。
Beach Boy.
给我们一个很好提示。
No? He took your money, too.
300万，你可以abc无论你想要。
"La Reina" says to do it.
行吗？
Elena, please...
Make her watch.
开始说话。
Let me do it.
- 我想看到钱。abc- 我在车上。
Not you, "Caviar."
收下吧。
It's my gift to him.
把球传给正确...
- 截球进球abc- 你到底是谁？
了我孩子们想法abc从策略海伦娜书。
如果你想控制别人，abc他们所爱东西。
解放口
O。
您正在做
- 你是对家伙吗？abc- 坚持住，我们来救你。
So, I read up on your Buddha.
- 你想要什么？abc- 关闭他妈。
According to the Dalai Lama,
您必须停止并认识到，你是不是abc更多头海伦娜。
if you are in a position to prevent greater violence,
我们，你明白吗？
strike first and strike fast.
- 我们还没有听说过，说出来。abc- 我明白了。
下面是如何去。abc你父亲与你同在。
Alex kidnapped people, Ben.
?与我们同在，
He had people
没有钱，你什么都没有。
tortured and killed.
如果有不同 -
So have we.
将抛头颅，洒热血。abc你明白吗？
我明白了。
我感兴趣只是玛格达？
Dennis fucked us
on those files.
多么美好
而如果这是一个变化abc行为，
When Alex was up there,
he begged Elena on
the head of Magda,
her daughter.
，你必须证明这一点。
在一个地方，在一个小时O端口abc我们选择。
Which means
she must be alive.
And Dennis knows.
我们玛格达，而不是abc采取任何其他。
Yeah.
如果你不按照计划，甚至abc在更多细节，
We're short three mil.
Another hit
is problematic.
这个女孩会死，abc非常痛苦。
We have got to squeeze it out of Dennis somehow.
法鲁一切你说。
Find her and trade her.
You mean, "Kidnap."
我听说了。
BEN: The same as O.
You up for that?
Yeah.
I am.
Daddy, there's a man here to see you.
我告诉你，这将是abc来，让我。
What man?
- 把她带走。abc- 操海伦那。
I don't know.
她离开这里
出来了
I was driving by
your neighborgood
and noticed that your yard needs some trimming.
My crew would like to give you a free haircut today.
My wife usually takes care of that stuff.
Sarah, Hannah, go to your room right now.
But, Daddy...
No "buts," no nothing. Go.
Papa says, "Go."
Lado! You come to my house?
You threaten my daughters?
You don't think I'm the kind of guy that
把它放在椅子上。
doesn't have cameras all over the place?
It don't matter to me.
After I whack you
and your daughters,
I'll burn the house down.
我知道你们是好。
Come on, you found
your fucking snitch.
非常好。abc我得到了它。
You found him.
索非亚，更遑论与abc老太太。
What happened to your hand?
(ENGINE REVVING)
多么美妙大团圆结局。
DENNIS: Got it caught
在你回家之前，
in a weed whacker.
Weed whacker?
我想告诉你一件事。
Yeah.
"Weed whacker," my ass.
We need to have a conversation.
Because I'm confused about some of your actions, Dennis.
Like what?
Like you giving Ben and Chon all that information.
You must be smoking
your own shit now, man.
You got to know
I'm your man.
I got you your
green card, okay?
I've been protecting you
for six fucking years.
Now that shit
hits the fan,
you got seven dead beaners, you got a white lawyer in Laguna,
you need me now
more than ever.
啊，你错过了最精彩部分。
Stop begging.
You sound like a woman.
Dennis,abcI know you gave them stuff.
What makes you so goddamn sure it's not Azul?
Because I know it wasn't him.
What do you mean?
Because I'm working
with him now, anfibi o.
What?
And you lie to
me one more time,
motherfucker,
I will shoot you down.
Since when have you
been working with Azul?
You're not going
to tell me that?
Since two days ago.
我会让感觉，宝贝。
I never gave them you, Lado.abcThey had me.
I'd be out of business.
I'd be useless to you.
I never thought this Iraq psycho would go nuts on you guys.
Akido，卢卡，昆...
I never gave you up, ever!
职位呢？
I'm your best friend
on this side, man.
这，老板，好吧。
Did you tell them I
was your little snitch?
What are you, crazy?abcWhat would be in it for me?
Answer me, Dennis.
正如我在开始时所说，
I gave them
enough to just get them
off my fucking ass...
我可能不会活着结束时。
Yes or no?
No!
No, okay? No. No.
只是因为我们发明abc关于自己故事，
It's all about you and me, and that's it!
并不意味着我们可以abc人们所期望。
You have got to believe me this time, man.
原因吗？，
I don't want to
lose this shit!
没有人土地。
I got two fucking kids
在中间沙漠。
and a wife that's dying.
我们有一条线abc从这里射出两英里。
Thank you, Dennis.abcNow they got my $3 million.
我们并不孤单，有三个人abc左侧碱，
And I want that money.
It's my money! It's my money!
2200码。
Fuckers.abcYou can't trust anybody no more. Fuck!
好了，我们知道这会发生。abc让他们在枪口下。
I can't even
trust my fucking wife.
不要让他们拍摄abc单杆。行吗？
She's looking to
divorce me, you know?
我们涵盖肩膀。
My wife's barely breathing.abcWelcome to midlife crisis, buddy.
准备拍摄人。
How do you know you can trust this Azul guy?
想想在这样OK吗？abc你已经死了。
I mean, come on.
Has he given you a piece of the business?abcIs that what he promised you?
在你出生那天，你就死定了，abc接受这样朋友，
Because Elena is not
going to fold that easy.
并接受任何东西。
You know, that
three million is
her money.
我们在股权朋友abc玩了。
Now, don't be a knucklehead.abcThink.
Fuck you.abcYou think, you fucked it up.
我告诉过你，我爱你吗？
How are you
going to get me back
my money?
(STAMMERS)
，今天上午。
You need me.
I'm going to get
you your money.
But they need the girl.
The guys want this girl.
好了，所以。
They're in fucking love with this chick.
And they want O, okay?
So, where is she?
I don't have her.
What do you mean,
you "don't have her"?
Where is she?
With Elena.
In Mexico?
No, here.
Here?
Some fucking
Indian reservation.
Elena came to
see her daughter.
An now that woman
is in my face, telling me
what to do, provoking me.
Oh, this is big, man.
"La Reina" Elena
is on US soil?
I told you, it's Indian land.abcShe's protected.
And I'm going to fix that.abcThat's why you need Dennis.abcThink.
Stop telling me to think.
No, no, no, man.
Look, these guys, they got the three million.
What do you think they're going to do with it?
They're going to
fucking give it
to Elena, right?
And we, first, are going to sell them Elena's daughter.
We split the profits,
and then we fuck Elena!
Fuck her!
首先，让我们O.
Do you understand?
Whoa!
现在。
转到本。
OPHELIA: Dennis wanted $3 mi II i o n. The b o ys wanted Magda.
我给我女儿。
Dennis, as usua I, was o ne step ahead.
I'd like to blow your fucking heads off.
现在。
They threatened my daughters.abcMy daughters!
去
Enough with the whining.
You deserve every fucking inch of your pain, asshole.
You gave us up.
它结束了，亲爱。
Like I had a choice.
不要碰我。abc我不想再见到你。
You could have gone along.abcYou would have made big money.
- 离我远点。abc- Magdita。
But you had to pull your Iraq GI Jack shit.
We want Magda.
Ask your smart-ass boy, here.abcSEAL boy, hey.
这是办公室，好吗？你是安全。
Did you figure it out from the transcripts?
All the calls
to Orange County?
我已经答应了。
Where the fuck is she?
What's in it for me?
Your life, which I'm about to take.
I'm dead either way.
我们就大功告成了。
But the thought of you sitting
in a prison cell for the rest of your life
我不需要看你abc再次感谢您。
gives me great afterlife pleasure.
我们从这里走。
A million in cash,
for Magda's location.
Say goodbye to your wife,
take your girls and go.
来吧。
Three mil.
Or no deal.abcThat's my walk-away price.
Walk away from what,
Dennis?
Nobody wants you.
Magda is your only hope.
最后一件事，鱼子酱。
Three mil, take it or leave it.
Throw in your snitch.
The three mil,
you can do whatever
you want with it.
我间谍谁？
All right?
Start talking.
When I see the money.
It's in the car.
你儿子...
Get it.
你不应该骗我
(BELL CHIMING)
覆盖它们。
死还是活，谁拥有abc在鸣枪。
What the fuck you want?
(GROANS)
他妈是着火了
国家修复男孩。
OPHELIA: My b o ys t oo k a page fr o m E I ena's p I ayb oo k.
没有，你会怎么做？妈
I f y o u want t o c o ntr oI s o meb o dy, take what they Io ve.
(MAGDA SCREAMING)
Fuck!
运行，拍摄，拍摄。
No, no, no!
开始
停止，狗娘养。
(MUFFLED SOBS)
- 好，坐吧。abc- 注意，覆盖，覆盖，覆盖。
去
妈妈告诉妈妈abc我爱你妈妈
Take her gag off.
O, h o w are y o u
h oI ding up?
不，不，不，不。
Are you guys okay?
Y o u hang in there, baby.
We're c o ming f o r y o u.
帮助玛格达。
What do you want?
BEN: Shut the fuck up.
Y o u want t o start
by understanding
帮助玛格达。abc省省吧。
y o u're n o t in charge anym o re, E I ena.
在这里，我们走吧。
We are.
D o y o u understand?
D o n't n o d. Say it.
I understand.
This is how
it's to work.
Your daughter
goes with you,
O comes with us.
N o m o ney, n o n o thing.
We go our separate ways and we live our separate lives.
Do you understand?
I understand.
I only care about Magda.
That's very sweet.
And if that reflects
a change of attitude,
you'll have to prove it.
You bring O
to a place we designate,
at a time we designate.
We exchange Magda.
Y o u bring n o o ne e I se.
You deviate from the plan
in any minute detail,
and the girl
will die very badly.
I'll do anything you say.
(GROANS)
You'll hear from us.
(MAGDA SCREAMING)
我不拍。
奥菲莉亚...我有一个家庭，
儿童，请。
I told you they
would come for me.
Get her out of here.
Fuck you, Elena.
Get her out of here!
Out!
(SOBBING)
本。
海角，我们已经做出来，abc区安全。
好。
春
请帮助他。
Put her on the chair.
没关系。
I enjoyed that.
Your boys did good.
Real good.
Juancario, Sophia,
leave me alone
with the sen o rita.
就要死了。
春，我不会离开他。
It's almost over.
不
With a happy ending.
But before you go home,
I want to show you something.
(OPHELIA GASPING)
这是一个伟大地方，
砂...水...
星星，
(SCREAMING)
幸福人 -
笑容。
Oh, you missed
the best part.
我冷。
这我怎么abc我想象中，
，但有一个不同现实真相。
I'll be in touch, baby.
DENNIS: D o y o u remember
my graduati o n day?
I'll never forget
the way you looked at me
when I got my badge.
发生了什么事abc搞砸了枪战。
他得到了第二个给了每个人abc可能性。
You were so proud.
But, you know,
they don't tell you when
they give you the badge
the river of shit
you're going to have
to wade through.
And the joke is, they don't want you to get any of that shit on you.
They want you to
walk through it clean,
but what's clean anymore?
I have to go to my supervisor, and he takes his taste and...
If you want to see
the real crooks,
the real pros,
just turn on
the fucking TV.
Yeah.
We've made heroes of whores.abcA nation of whores.
我们说一个人，海伦娜。
我你，我们abc我们来到这里。
Wall Street. Washington.
Those bastards make
what I do out here
look pathetic.
狙击手？
If they woke up
with my job,
告诉他放下武器abc举手，
with my life,
with my salary,
they'd be looking
for the nearest
gun to swallow.
或进入吉普车，离开。
You can't stop.
You can't climb out.
把它给我。
No left turns,
no right turns.
It's just a circle and everybody gets their cut.
你想怎样做呢？
I can't tell you the last thing that I saw that was completely clean.
再见吧，亲爱
Except you.
Except you on that day.
GO GO
玛格达
丹尼斯，他不能离开abc3亿美元，不得不采取行动。
Aqui, WKQ.
You in positions?
去吧，去吧。
Si, jefe, esta bien.
洛林海伦娜，我们找到你了。
OPHELIA: Like I said in the beginning,
I might n o t be a I ive at the end.
再次今天，abc我们采取行动
Just because we make up st o ries ab o ut o urse I ves
保护我们孩子abc我们自由。
d o esn't mean we can escape what waits f o r us.
丹尼斯我向你保证，吸引了abc非常小心论文。
BEN: Why here?
由于拆除abc卡特尔领导，
CHON: It's a wide bowl.
Old Indian burial ground.
中，共查获了一系列abc在我国药物。
Doc can get a line of sight for up to two miles here.
任何保留，而不是技术上abc我们国家，但我们知道它。
DOC: We're not alone.
Three men, left side of the basin, about 2,000 to 2,300 yards.
所以...
All right, we knew this was going to happen.
海伦娜责任，abc走了30年在监狱里。
Wait unti I we get a h oI d o f O.abcAnd, D o c...
Don't let them get off
more than one
shot each, all right?
We got your back.abcLet's set up shop, boys.
海伦娜比赛中，abc并没有干扰丹尼斯，
拉多他手下，abc创建一个新迹象。
Think of it like this, all right?
You're already dead.
阿祖尔拉多
You were dead
the moment you were born.
If you accept that,
you can accept anything.
笨笨abc看到了在丹尼斯。
It's been a ride, man.abcI've enjoyed it.
丹尼斯识别本春，如
为举报人保密abc在过去6年。
Have I ever told you
that I love you, man?
他照顾他们。
Yeah, this morning.
但谁真正值得信赖那些谁
Well, I do.
我不知道。
本春推移，一些abc周在监狱里，然后...
好了，消失了。
。
说，我们是在非洲，
在肯尼亚，
或一些神奇岛屿abc在印度尼西亚。
保持对话abc草春本
本冲浪有时，abc在今年。
事情发生 -
You give us O first.
永远不能回去。
Now.
我需要一段时间，abc但我回来再住。
Go to Ben. Go to Ben.
Give me my daughter!
Now!
Go.
我不知道，我敢肯定，你将能够abc有3个恋爱中人。
Don't touch me!
I'm never going
to see you again.
是行不通方式。
I'm getting
the fuck out of here!
Magdita...
我想定义abc贝尔瓦。
手段残忍，激烈 -
It's loaded, okay?
Okay.
Keep safe.
Keep down, okay?
回归到原始状态。
有一天，或许我们会回来。
We're finished.
We don't need to
see you again, thanks.
We're out of here.
但现在，我们生活abc野兽。
Vam o s?
美丽野兽
Just one last thing,
"Caviar."
Who's my rat?
(BLOWS KISS)
You ungrateful piece of...
You should've fucked me.
(GROANS)
Team leader down!abcWho's got the tango at my six?
All right, Jesse.
Shoot whatever the fuck you got! Go!
Come on, guys!abcIt's raining bullets, here.
What the fuck are you doing?
Shit! Move, Sam!
Chief, should we shift?
Negative, stay put!
Go!
Oh, fuck!
Smoke that motherfucker.
DOC: Sam, cover Ben!
BILLY: Move! Cover me, cover me! Hold!
Move!
Mommy, Mommy!
I love you, Mommy!
No, no, no!
Help Magda.
Save Magda. Save Magda.
Get out of here!
Go, come on!
(GUN FIRES)
Fuck!
Don't shoot.
Please, Ophelia.
I have a family.
Three little ones, you know?abcPlease.
Ben!
DOC: Chief, they t oo k o ff.abcWe're c o ming in.
H oI d o n.abcWe'll be there in 10 o r I ess.
Chon?
Please, help him.
(BEN GASPS)
OPHELIA: Shh... It's okay.
It's okay.
He's going to die.
Chon,abcI don't want to leave him.
No.
(GASPS)
You're really going to love it there.
Soft water.
Stars.
And the people
smile...
(ALL GASPING)
I'm cold.
OPHELIA: That's the wayabcI imagined it.
But the truth has a mind o f its o wn.
What rea II y happened was m o re o f a fuck-up than a sh oo t-o ut.
And gave us a II a sec o nd chance.
CHON: We said
"alone," Elena.
I am one, you are two.abcLet's just do what we came to do.
And the snipers.
Tell them to put
the scopes on the ground,
hands in the air.
Or we're back in
the jeep and we're gone.
Get rid of them.
ELENA: So how do you
want to do this?
(ENGINE STARTING)
Adi o s, amiguitas.
(HELICOPTER APPROACHING)
Go, go!
Magda!
OPHELIA: And oI d Dennis, wh o c o u I dn't I eave t o wn with his three mi I
had t o h o rn in o n the acti o n.
Go! Go!
Run!
"La Reina" Elena!
We gotcha!
DENNIS: T o day, we have made great strides
t o further pr o tect o ur chi I dren and o ur freed o ms.
OPHELIA: And Dennis sure made a big sh o t o f himse I f o n the news.
By dismant I ing the I eadership o f the Baja carte I
and the curse o f i II icit drugs in o ur c o untry.
I t is an I ndian reservati o n.abcI t is technica II y n o t o ur c o untry.
But, as we kn o w, it is.abc(LAUGHS) S o...
OPHELIA: E I ena t oo k the fa II and went t o pris o n f o r 30 years.
With E I ena o ut o f the picture,
and Dennis running interference,
Lad o and Azu I created a new carte I.
The Azu I at o s.
Ben being Ben, he had the g oo ds o n Dennis.
And Dennis, identifying Ben and Ch o n as his c o nfidentia I inf o rmants
f o r the I ast six years, t oo k care o f them.
But wh o rea II y trusted wh o?
I have n o idea.
Ben and Ch o n spent a c o up I e o f weeks in the s I ammer
and then, we II, vanished.
Like I did.
They say we're in Africa
o ff Kenya.
O r s o me magic is I and in I nd o nesia.
They sti II ta I k ab o utabcBen and Ch o n's herb.
And it surfaces every n o w and then o ver the years.
These things that happened...
Y o u can never g o back.
I t t oo k me a whi I e,
but I began t o I ive again.
I'm n o t s o sure there can ever be three pe o p I e equa II y in Io ve.
I tjust d o esn't w o rk that way.
I loo ked up the definiti o n o f "savage."
I t means, "Crue I, cripp I ed.
"Regressed back t o a prima I state o f being."
O ne day, maybe, we'll be back.
F o r n o w, we I ive I ike savages.
Beautifu I savages.